<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?> 
<sphinx:docset xmlns:sphinx="http://sphinxsearch.com">

<sphinx:document id="9270095736706771532">
 <title><![CDATA[Best new iPhone, iPad and Android games for August 2012]]></title>
 <h><![CDATA[<a href='http://i-cdn.phonearena.com/images/article/33724-thumb/Best-new-iPhone-iPad-and-Android-games-for-August-2012.jpg' target=_blank><img src='http://i-cdn.phonearena.com/images/article/33724-thumb/Best-new-iPhone-iPad-and-Android-games-for-August-2012.jpg' title='size: 0 width: 0 height: 0'></a>iPad
iPhone
Android
∧iPad
∧iPhone
∧Android http://phonearena.com/news/Best-new-iPhone-iPad-and-Android-games-for-August-2012_id33724 Android
iPad
iPhone
∧Android
∧iPad
∧iPhone ]]></h>
 <alt><![CDATA[2,8,32,128]]></alt>
 <bodys><![CDATA[∧mobile∧operating∧systems, ∧products, ∧tablet∧computers August has come and gone and we hope you've got those summer memories all ready to be packed in a cozy place in your mind as September and the fall nears. Good news is that the bad weather is a good excuse for staying...]]></bodys>
 <bodyn><![CDATA[10101010]]></bodyn>
 <meta><![CDATA[731]]></meta>
 <ref><![CDATA[93]]></ref>
 <url><![CDATA[http://api.snatz.com/index.php?app=asmapi&event=feeds&time=new&feed_id=10165606831038527961&item_id=13242450258640478110-12-09]]></url>
 <cdate>1376321299</cdate>
 <mmedia>0</mmedia>
 <bseo>0</bseo>
 <uid>2</uid>
 <sid>1</sid>
 <lang>255</lang>
 <afflags0>2,8,32,128</afflags0>
 <afflags1>30</afflags1>
 <afflags2>18</afflags2>
 <afflags3>2,8,32,128</afflags3>
 <afflags4>2,8,32,128</afflags4>
 <afflags5>2,8,32,128</afflags5>
 <afflags6>2,8,32,128</afflags6>
 <afflags7>2,8,32,128</afflags7>

 <afflags0ex>1,4,16,64</afflags0ex>
 <afflags1ex>1,4,16,64</afflags1ex>
 <afflags2ex>1,4,16,64</afflags2ex>
 <afflags3ex>1,4,16,64</afflags3ex>
 <afflags4ex>1,4,16,64</afflags4ex>
 <afflags5ex>1,4,16,64</afflags5ex>
 <afflags6ex>1,4,16,64</afflags6ex>
 <afflags7ex>1,4,16,64</afflags7ex>
</sphinx:document>
<sphinx:document id="9270106130186420564">
 <title><![CDATA[Happy July 4th, American automakers]]></title>
 <h><![CDATA[auto industry
∧auto∧industry http://reviews.cnet.com/8301-13746_7-57466262-48/happy-july-4th-american-automakers/?part=rss&subj=news&tag=title ]]></h>
 <alt><![CDATA[2,8,32,128]]></alt>
 <bodys><![CDATA[Celebrate the American auto industry with all-American nameplates.
[Read more]]]></bodys>
 <bodyn><![CDATA[10101010]]></bodyn>
 <meta><![CDATA[593]]></meta>
 <ref><![CDATA[93]]></ref>
 <url><![CDATA[http://api.snatz.com/index.php?app=asmapi&event=feeds&time=new&feed_id=11221331071403660916&item_id=10333153592555262102-12-07]]></url>
 <cdate>1376321299</cdate>
 <mmedia>0</mmedia>
 <bseo>0</bseo>
 <uid>2</uid>
 <sid>1</sid>
 <lang>255</lang>
 <afflags0>1</afflags0>
 <afflags1>24</afflags1>
 <afflags2>18</afflags2>
 <afflags3>2,8,32,128</afflags3>
 <afflags4>2,8,32,128</afflags4>
 <afflags5>2,8,32,128</afflags5>
 <afflags6>2,8,32,128</afflags6>
 <afflags7>2,8,32,128</afflags7>

 <afflags0ex>1,4,16,64</afflags0ex>
 <afflags1ex>1,4,16,64</afflags1ex>
 <afflags2ex>1,4,16,64</afflags2ex>
 <afflags3ex>1,4,16,64</afflags3ex>
 <afflags4ex>1,4,16,64</afflags4ex>
 <afflags5ex>1,4,16,64</afflags5ex>
 <afflags6ex>1,4,16,64</afflags6ex>
 <afflags7ex>1,4,16,64</afflags7ex>
</sphinx:document>
<sphinx:document id="9270126698649279031">
 <title><![CDATA[ZTE, Alcatel, Huawei, and LG will make Firefox OS phones: coming with apps like Facebook, Twitter, Cut The Rope]]></title>
 <h><![CDATA[<a href='http://i-cdn.phonearena.com/images/article/40146-thumb/ZTE-Alcatel-Huawei-and-LG-will-make-Firefox-OS-phones-coming-with-apps-like-Facebook-Twitter-Cut-The-Rope.jpg' target=_blank><img src='http://i-cdn.phonearena.com/images/article/40146-thumb/ZTE-Alcatel-Huawei-and-LG-will-make-Firefox-OS-phones-coming-with-apps-like-Facebook-Twitter-Cut-The-Rope.jpg' title='size: 0 width: 0 height: 0'></a>LG
Firefox OS
ZTE
Twitter
Mozilla
Huawei
Alcatel
Facebook
phone maker
announce
Cut the Rope
∧LG
∧Firefox∧OS
∧ZTE
∧Twitter
∧Mozilla
∧Huawei
∧Alcatel
∧Facebook
∧phone∧maker
∧announce
∧Cut∧the∧Rope http://phonearena.com/news/ZTE-Alcatel-Huawei-and-LG-will-make-Firefox-OS-phones-coming-with-apps-like-Facebook-Twitter-Cut-The-Rope_id40146 Cut the Rope
Facebook
Firefox OS
Huawei
LG
Mozilla
Twitter
announce
∧Cut∧the∧Rope
∧Facebook
∧Firefox∧OS
∧Huawei
∧LG
∧Mozilla
∧Twitter
∧announce ]]></h>
 <alt><![CDATA[2,8,32,128]]></alt>
 <bodys><![CDATA[∧companies, ∧dic∧events, ∧games, ∧mobile∧operating∧systems, ∧social∧network∧sites Mozilla has just announced that it got four phone makers on board its brand new HTML5-based Firefox OS. LG, Huawei, ZTE and Alcatel are the ones…]]></bodys>
 <bodyn><![CDATA[10101010]]></bodyn>
 <meta><![CDATA[765]]></meta>
 <ref><![CDATA[94]]></ref>
 <url><![CDATA[http://api.snatz.com/index.php?app=asmapi&event=feeds&time=new&feed_id=10165606831038527961&item_id=11511804581894438319-13-02]]></url>
 <cdate>1376321299</cdate>
 <mmedia>0</mmedia>
 <bseo>0</bseo>
 <uid>2</uid>
 <sid>1</sid>
 <lang>255</lang>
 <afflags0>2</afflags0>
 <afflags1>30</afflags1>
 <afflags2>18</afflags2>
 <afflags3>2,8,32,128</afflags3>
 <afflags4>2,8,32,128</afflags4>
 <afflags5>2,8,32,128</afflags5>
 <afflags6>2,8,32,128</afflags6>
 <afflags7>2,8,32,128</afflags7>

 <afflags0ex>1,4,16,64</afflags0ex>
 <afflags1ex>1,4,16,64</afflags1ex>
 <afflags2ex>1,4,16,64</afflags2ex>
 <afflags3ex>1,4,16,64</afflags3ex>
 <afflags4ex>1,4,16,64</afflags4ex>
 <afflags5ex>1,4,16,64</afflags5ex>
 <afflags6ex>1,4,16,64</afflags6ex>
 <afflags7ex>1,4,16,64</afflags7ex>
</sphinx:document>
<sphinx:document id="9270145872697286359">
 <title><![CDATA[NBA Gives Basketball Nerds the Gift of Big Data]]></title>
 <h><![CDATA[<a href='http://4.mshcdn.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/02/NBAstatssite.png' target=_blank><img src='http://4.mshcdn.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/02/NBAstatssite.png' title='size: 0 width: 0 height: 0'></a>NBA
tool
∧NBA
∧tool
∧∧NBA http://mashable.com/2013/02/14/nba-stats-data/ ]]></h>
 <alt><![CDATA[2,8,32,128]]></alt>
 <bodys><![CDATA[A new tool introduced by the NBA gives hardcore and casual hoops fans alike access to an overwhelming amount of historical stats and data. More About: NBA, Sports]]></bodys>
 <bodyn><![CDATA[10101010]]></bodyn>
 <meta><![CDATA[622]]></meta>
 <ref><![CDATA[93]]></ref>
 <url><![CDATA[http://api.snatz.com/index.php?app=asmapi&event=segments&segment=0&type=c&item=18114138564421745587-13-02]]></url>
 <cdate>1376321299</cdate>
 <mmedia>0</mmedia>
 <bseo>0</bseo>
 <uid>2</uid>
 <sid>1</sid>
 <lang>255</lang>
 <afflags0>2,8,32,128</afflags0>
 <afflags1>24</afflags1>
 <afflags2>18</afflags2>
 <afflags3>2,8,32,128</afflags3>
 <afflags4>2,8,32,128</afflags4>
 <afflags5>2,8,32,128</afflags5>
 <afflags6>2,8,32,128</afflags6>
 <afflags7>2,8,32,128</afflags7>

 <afflags0ex>1,4,16,64</afflags0ex>
 <afflags1ex>1,4,16,64</afflags1ex>
 <afflags2ex>1,4,16,64</afflags2ex>
 <afflags3ex>1,4,16,64</afflags3ex>
 <afflags4ex>1,4,16,64</afflags4ex>
 <afflags5ex>1,4,16,64</afflags5ex>
 <afflags6ex>1,4,16,64</afflags6ex>
 <afflags7ex>1,4,16,64</afflags7ex>
</sphinx:document>
<sphinx:document id="9270157102582891449">
 <title><![CDATA[Cloud Computing and Your Small Biz: Is It a Match Made in Heaven?]]></title>
 <h><![CDATA[CDW
∧CDW http://smartdatacollective.com/ephraimcohen/100781/cloud-computing-and-your-small-biz-it-match-made-heaven ]]></h>
 <alt><![CDATA[2,8,32,128]]></alt>
 <bodys><![CDATA[Cloud computing — you’ve heard of it, you may even be using it without realizing it. And the technology is beginning to catch on, according to a 2011 Cloud Computing Tracking Poll conducted by CDW, a provider of technology solutions. What is it exactly, and what potential benefits does it offer for your small business?]]></bodys>
 <bodyn><![CDATA[10101010]]></bodyn>
 <meta><![CDATA[862]]></meta>
 <ref><![CDATA[93]]></ref>
 <url><![CDATA[http://api.snatz.com/index.php?app=asmapi&event=feeds&time=new&feed_id=10357133489699587377&item_id=14586093596142254246-13-02]]></url>
 <cdate>1376321299</cdate>
 <mmedia>0</mmedia>
 <bseo>0</bseo>
 <uid>2</uid>
 <sid>1</sid>
 <lang>255</lang>
 <afflags0>3</afflags0>
 <afflags1>24</afflags1>
 <afflags2>18</afflags2>
 <afflags3>2,8,32,128</afflags3>
 <afflags4>2,8,32,128</afflags4>
 <afflags5>2,8,32,128</afflags5>
 <afflags6>2,8,32,128</afflags6>
 <afflags7>2,8,32,128</afflags7>

 <afflags0ex>1,4,16,64</afflags0ex>
 <afflags1ex>1,4,16,64</afflags1ex>
 <afflags2ex>1,4,16,64</afflags2ex>
 <afflags3ex>1,4,16,64</afflags3ex>
 <afflags4ex>1,4,16,64</afflags4ex>
 <afflags5ex>1,4,16,64</afflags5ex>
 <afflags6ex>1,4,16,64</afflags6ex>
 <afflags7ex>1,4,16,64</afflags7ex>
</sphinx:document>
<sphinx:document id="9270165583498308875">
 <title><![CDATA[It's not my dog]]></title>
 <h><![CDATA[<a href='http://i.ytimg.com/vi/tIsa05fXfog/mqdefault.jpg' target=_blank><img src='http://i.ytimg.com/vi/tIsa05fXfog/mqdefault.jpg' title='size: 0 width: 0 height: 0'></a>dog
∧dog http://cutbit.com/its-not-my-dog-video_23633f790.html ]]></h>
 <alt><![CDATA[2,8,32,128]]></alt>
 <bodys><![CDATA[It&apos;s not my dog]]></bodys>
 <bodyn><![CDATA[10101010]]></bodyn>
 <meta><![CDATA[455]]></meta>
 <ref><![CDATA[93]]></ref>
 <url><![CDATA[http://api.snatz.com/index.php?app=asmapi&event=feeds&time=new&feed_id=15663532496881534248&item_id=11180733967424306432-13-02]]></url>
 <cdate>1376321299</cdate>
 <mmedia>0</mmedia>
 <bseo>0</bseo>
 <uid>2</uid>
 <sid>1</sid>
 <lang>255</lang>
 <afflags0>2,8,32,128</afflags0>
 <afflags1>24</afflags1>
 <afflags2>1</afflags2>
 <afflags3>2,8,32,128</afflags3>
 <afflags4>2,8,32,128</afflags4>
 <afflags5>2,8,32,128</afflags5>
 <afflags6>2,8,32,128</afflags6>
 <afflags7>2,8,32,128</afflags7>

 <afflags0ex>1,4,16,64</afflags0ex>
 <afflags1ex>1,4,16,64</afflags1ex>
 <afflags2ex>1,4,16,64</afflags2ex>
 <afflags3ex>1,4,16,64</afflags3ex>
 <afflags4ex>1,4,16,64</afflags4ex>
 <afflags5ex>1,4,16,64</afflags5ex>
 <afflags6ex>1,4,16,64</afflags6ex>
 <afflags7ex>1,4,16,64</afflags7ex>
</sphinx:document>
<sphinx:document id="9270187494013135858">
 <title><![CDATA[An organizer's unconference]]></title>
 <h><![CDATA[<a href='http://www.frogloop.com/storage/images/Ned.JPG?__SQUARESPACE_CACHEVERSION=1353955578011' target=_blank><img src='http://www.frogloop.com/storage/images/Ned.JPG?__SQUARESPACE_CACHEVERSION=1353955578011' title='size: 0 width: 0 height: 0'></a>RootsCamp
∧RootsCamp http://frogloop.com/care2blog/2012/11/26/an-organizers-unconference.html Care2
∧Care2 ]]></h>
 <alt><![CDATA[2,8,32,128]]></alt>
 <bodys><![CDATA[∧web∧services With the taillights of Election 2012 now at a comfortable distance, Progressives have a lot to buzz about -- what went well, what could've gone better, and what lessons can be learned from this election cycle to build an advantage in the next. While many of these conversations are already heard from political pundits and campaign strategists, where it really counts is when the organizers themselves gather together and hash out ideas, give feedback, share best practices, and renew their plans for victory.
This is all set to happen at this week's&nbsp;New Organizing Institute (NOI)'s RootsCamp National 2012 unconference (Nov 30th and Dec 1st, here in D.C.) -- a mecca of sorts for the organizer faithful. And with an expected 2,000 attendees, dozens upon dozens of impromptu sessions, as well as a bustling career fair, this year's event is set to build substantially on previous years' efforts.
RootsCamp was the first "unconference" I ever attended, and it pretty much sold me on the unconference model and how it sparked earnest, passionate, spontaneous discussion among a variety of players. There is a real energy there, unlike any other event, and leaves you with this enchanted feeling that you're seeing exactly where the rubber meets the road.
The Care2 Team has sponsored and attended RootsCamp for years and always leaves impressed with the experience. I asked some of my teammates to also share a few words about their experience at this event:
&nbsp;
I attended RootsCamp last year for the first time and was impressed by the energy, passion and enthusiasm of the organizers and participants. &nbsp;The sessions, although seemingly organized on the fly in the unconference style, were very thoughtful and informative. &nbsp; I met some great people who are doing great things in the world. &nbsp;It was one of the best conferences I attended last year.
-Molly Connors, Director of Nonprofit Services
&nbsp;
RootsCamp is full of excited and inspiring advocacy campaigners -- all from the Progressive movement.&nbsp;It's a fun event attended by a lot of Care2 clients and the "unconference" format ensures that it's never dull. Care2 is very much a proud member of this tribe of people who are trying to change the world, and that's why we look forward to this event each year.
-Clint O'Brien, VP Nonprofit Services
&nbsp;
Last year was my first RootsCamp and I loved it. It's a high energy, well organized gathering of activists sharing best practices and ideas with each other. And, it's great for networking!
-Ashley Hansen, Director of Nonprofit Services
&nbsp;
&nbsp;
RootsCamp brings together some of the smartest most dedicated organizers around. The energy, passion and creativity of the participants is really inspiring.
-Eric Rardin, Senior Director of Nonprofit Services
&nbsp;
&nbsp;
You can&nbsp;register here for the RootsCamp National Unconference&nbsp;(November 30th - December 1st) and&nbsp;sign up here to attend a free RootsCamp Caucus Day event&nbsp;(Thursday, November 29th).
&nbsp;]]></bodys>
 <bodyn><![CDATA[10101010]]></bodyn>
 <meta><![CDATA[3485]]></meta>
 <ref><![CDATA[93]]></ref>
 <url><![CDATA[http://api.snatz.com/index.php?app=asmapi&event=feeds&time=new&feed_id=17501146315248466241&item_id=9955982531008879854-12-11]]></url>
 <cdate>1376321299</cdate>
 <mmedia>0</mmedia>
 <bseo>0</bseo>
 <uid>2</uid>
 <sid>1</sid>
 <lang>255</lang>
 <afflags0>2,8,32,128</afflags0>
 <afflags1>30</afflags1>
 <afflags2>1</afflags2>
 <afflags3>2,8,32,128</afflags3>
 <afflags4>2,8,32,128</afflags4>
 <afflags5>2,8,32,128</afflags5>
 <afflags6>2,8,32,128</afflags6>
 <afflags7>2,8,32,128</afflags7>

 <afflags0ex>1,4,16,64</afflags0ex>
 <afflags1ex>1,4,16,64</afflags1ex>
 <afflags2ex>1,4,16,64</afflags2ex>
 <afflags3ex>1,4,16,64</afflags3ex>
 <afflags4ex>1,4,16,64</afflags4ex>
 <afflags5ex>1,4,16,64</afflags5ex>
 <afflags6ex>1,4,16,64</afflags6ex>
 <afflags7ex>1,4,16,64</afflags7ex>
</sphinx:document>
<sphinx:document id="9270188585127644062">
 <title><![CDATA[Back To Basics: Capturing Time]]></title>
 <h><![CDATA[<a href='http://cloud.lomography.com/576/380/17/658b9b69e467685fc2a5c3afb88c1e6b0f0e29.jpg' target=_blank><img src='http://cloud.lomography.com/576/380/17/658b9b69e467685fc2a5c3afb88c1e6b0f0e29.jpg' title='size: 0 width: 0 height: 0'></a>Einstein
∧Einstein http://lomography.com/magazine/tipster/2012/10/29/back-to-basics-capturing-time Aperture
Holga
Sharp
∧Aperture
∧Holga
∧Sharp ]]></h>
 <alt><![CDATA[2,8,32,128]]></alt>
 <bodys><![CDATA[∧applications, ∧companies, ∧photographic∧equipment∧makers Einstein may have denounced the possibility of time travel, but the greatest thing about our first love, photography, is that it gives us the ability to stop time. This final Back to Basics article gives you the power to choose how.
Photo by adam_g2000
Before you read on, you may wish to go through my previous articles. You will need to know about aperture and shutter speed to follow this one.
Your shutter speed and aperture do more than just allow you to control depth of field, they allow you to choose how to stop time. As previously discussed, if your shutter has to stay open for a long time, you get camera shake if it’s handheld, whack that camera on a tripod or stable surface though, and using a cable release, you can fix everything except things in your frame that are moving.
Conversely, if you set a very high shutter speed (depending on the speed of the thing you are shooting) you can stop that movement with tack sharp clarity.
You can see in the picture below, that I’ve opened up the aperture of my SLR, and set a high film speed in an attempt to capture the droplets of water in this fountain. Something the eye has trouble doing.
Tripod 1/1000 of a second.
However in this picture below, I’ve done the opposite, I’ve closed the aperture down and set a slower film speed, thereby capturing the flow of the water for a more dreamy effect.
Tripod 1/8 of a second.
Making things flow, blurry people crossing streets, flowing water, etc. is fairly easy and can be done with most cameras (more below), but stopping motion can require a very fast shutter speed and mostly only SLRs will allow you to do this. The shutter speed required to freeze time without blur will depend entirely on what you are shooting and how far away it is. A train, 10s of meters away from you may be ‘stoppable’ with 1/100, closer it could be well over 1/1000.
Fast enough to stop the bubbles, but not enough to stop the movement.
For a very intense lesson on achieving this, check out How to Calculate a Minimum Shutter Speed to Yield an Adequately Sharp Image of a Moving Object, there is a great chart there with some rules of thumb.
As we’ve progressed over the past 8 months we’ve learned about the trilogy of variables required to get a perfect shot, we’ve now got to learn how to use them with finesse, especially for capturing movement. This is something that will take you practice to do, without flexible ISO, something that a digital camera can do, you may want to achieve both of these effects on the same roll of film. In order to do that you need to play around with a light meter, the one in an SLR will do, until you can grab the right film for the day. Read, Back To Basics: Film 101 and Back To Basics: Aperture and Depth of Field if this isn’t clear. Ultimately, you know that you are going to be locked into certain Aperture Values and Shutter Speeds, so you are going to have to carefully choose the ISO, the speed, of your film.
You don’t have to own an SLR to achieve these effects, but you do have to be able to override you camera. Automatic cameras like our favorite, the LC-A is pretty much out. A manual camera like the Lubitel is perfect for the job, with its range of apertures and shutter speeds, you can stop time or blur things. You’ve got complete control.
To browse this gallery please read this post on our website
A Diana, Holga or La Sardina is another matter, your shutter speed is fixed and the aperture isn’t going to make a big difference to your choice. You can see (if you read the distance chart) that you can freeze time at a distance, but close up, it’s a no go. It is easy though to blur things. You’ve got a wonderful trick up your sleeve on those cameras – the B (bulb) switch.
Set you camera to Bulb mode, whack it on a tripod, use a cable release, and you can open the shutter as long as you like, you just need to make sure your film is slow enough to provide you with a long enough exposure. A light meter will come in handy.
I won’t go into it here (it’s a story for another to tell), but the last word should go to Pinhole Photography. Due to its nature that all shots made this way are very slow.
To browse this gallery please read this post on our website
I hope you enjoyed this series of articles as much as I’ve enjoyed writing them. The biggest pleasure has been the discussions in the comments, and all the private messages I’ve had with questions, feedback or requests for more information. I thank you!
My new series will start next month, tentatively titled, ‘Basics Applied’. Each month I will select a Lomography camera and discuss it in terms of technical techniques and how to apply theory to said camera. I hope you will enjoy it.
We’re going out with a a bang! The team at Lomography have very kindly allowed me to suggest a Back to Basics Rumble, you can find that here, I look forward to seeing all your entries so get out there and show us what you’re made of!
And with that my friends, our time has come to an end!]]></bodys>
 <bodyn><![CDATA[10101010]]></bodyn>
 <meta><![CDATA[5483]]></meta>
 <ref><![CDATA[94]]></ref>
 <url><![CDATA[http://api.snatz.com/index.php?app=asmapi&event=feeds&time=new&feed_id=12794359493175214647&item_id=9806395442489389309-12-10]]></url>
 <cdate>1376321299</cdate>
 <mmedia>0</mmedia>
 <bseo>0</bseo>
 <uid>2</uid>
 <sid>1</sid>
 <lang>255</lang>
 <afflags0>2</afflags0>
 <afflags1>30</afflags1>
 <afflags2>1</afflags2>
 <afflags3>2,8,32,128</afflags3>
 <afflags4>2,8,32,128</afflags4>
 <afflags5>2,8,32,128</afflags5>
 <afflags6>2,8,32,128</afflags6>
 <afflags7>2,8,32,128</afflags7>

 <afflags0ex>1,4,16,64</afflags0ex>
 <afflags1ex>1,4,16,64</afflags1ex>
 <afflags2ex>1,4,16,64</afflags2ex>
 <afflags3ex>1,4,16,64</afflags3ex>
 <afflags4ex>1,4,16,64</afflags4ex>
 <afflags5ex>1,4,16,64</afflags5ex>
 <afflags6ex>1,4,16,64</afflags6ex>
 <afflags7ex>1,4,16,64</afflags7ex>
</sphinx:document>
<sphinx:document id="9270199648738367269">
 <title><![CDATA[Bandai resurrects Tamagotchi pets just in time for Valentine's Day]]></title>
 <h><![CDATA[Holiday
Bandai
Tamagotchi
∧Holiday
∧Bandai
∧Tamagotchi http://latimes.com/business/technology/la-fi-tn-tamagotchi-bandai-valentines-gift-android-20130214,0,2618494.story?track=rss Holiday
∧Holiday ]]></h>
 <alt><![CDATA[2,8,32,128]]></alt>
 <bodys><![CDATA[∧dic∧events If your significant other grew up in the '90s then unfortunately your Valentine's Day gift may be toppled this year by Bandai -- which has re-released its Tamagotchi pets for smartphones.]]></bodys>
 <bodyn><![CDATA[10101010]]></bodyn>
 <meta><![CDATA[744]]></meta>
 <ref><![CDATA[94]]></ref>
 <url><![CDATA[http://api.snatz.com/index.php?app=asmapi&event=feeds&time=new&feed_id=14910092466569186586&item_id=11726812368944103720-13-02]]></url>
 <cdate>1376321299</cdate>
 <mmedia>0</mmedia>
 <bseo>0</bseo>
 <uid>2</uid>
 <sid>1</sid>
 <lang>255</lang>
 <afflags0>2,8,32,128</afflags0>
 <afflags1>30</afflags1>
 <afflags2>1</afflags2>
 <afflags3>2,8,32,128</afflags3>
 <afflags4>2,8,32,128</afflags4>
 <afflags5>2,8,32,128</afflags5>
 <afflags6>2,8,32,128</afflags6>
 <afflags7>2,8,32,128</afflags7>

 <afflags0ex>1,4,16,64</afflags0ex>
 <afflags1ex>1,4,16,64</afflags1ex>
 <afflags2ex>1,4,16,64</afflags2ex>
 <afflags3ex>1,4,16,64</afflags3ex>
 <afflags4ex>1,4,16,64</afflags4ex>
 <afflags5ex>1,4,16,64</afflags5ex>
 <afflags6ex>1,4,16,64</afflags6ex>
 <afflags7ex>1,4,16,64</afflags7ex>
</sphinx:document>
<sphinx:document id="9270226136266237273">
 <title><![CDATA[Trailer]]></title>
 <h><![CDATA[<a href='http://assets1.ignimgs.com/vid/thumbnails/2013/04/17/21baf8fef50d4c00e30833b549c60a52-1366213728/frame_0000.jpg' target=_blank><img src='http://assets1.ignimgs.com/vid/thumbnails/2013/04/17/21baf8fef50d4c00e30833b549c60a52-1366213728/frame_0000.jpg' title='size: 0 width: 0 height: 0'></a>Square-Enix RPG
Trailer
∧Square∧Enix∧RPG
∧Trailer http://ign.com/videos/2013/04/17/bravely-default-flying-fairy-trailer ]]></h>
 <alt><![CDATA[2,8,32,128]]></alt>
 <bodys><![CDATA[Square-Enix's RPG heads West.]]></bodys>
 <bodyn><![CDATA[10101010]]></bodyn>
 <meta><![CDATA[472]]></meta>
 <ref><![CDATA[94]]></ref>
 <url><![CDATA[http://api.snatz.com/index.php?app=asmapi&event=feeds&time=new&feed_id=11265865173373524447&item_id=13380809143231013552-13-04]]></url>
 <cdate>1376321299</cdate>
 <mmedia>0</mmedia>
 <bseo>0</bseo>
 <uid>2</uid>
 <sid>1</sid>
 <lang>255</lang>
 <afflags0>2,8,32,128</afflags0>
 <afflags1>24</afflags1>
 <afflags2>1</afflags2>
 <afflags3>2,8,32,128</afflags3>
 <afflags4>2,8,32,128</afflags4>
 <afflags5>2,8,32,128</afflags5>
 <afflags6>2,8,32,128</afflags6>
 <afflags7>2,8,32,128</afflags7>

 <afflags0ex>1,4,16,64</afflags0ex>
 <afflags1ex>1,4,16,64</afflags1ex>
 <afflags2ex>1,4,16,64</afflags2ex>
 <afflags3ex>1,4,16,64</afflags3ex>
 <afflags4ex>1,4,16,64</afflags4ex>
 <afflags5ex>1,4,16,64</afflags5ex>
 <afflags6ex>1,4,16,64</afflags6ex>
 <afflags7ex>1,4,16,64</afflags7ex>
</sphinx:document>
<sphinx:document id="9270226403183706951">
 <title><![CDATA[TA Plays Bonus: 'Ridiculous Fishing' (With Vlambeer)]]></title>
 <h><![CDATA[<a href='http://cdn.toucharcade.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/03/831815_larger1.png' target=_blank><img src='http://cdn.toucharcade.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/03/831815_larger1.png' title='size: 0 width: 0 height: 0'></a>Bonus
Vlambeer
JW
Rami
TA
∧Bonus
∧Vlambeer
∧JW
∧Rami
∧TA http://toucharcade.com/2013/03/14/ta-plays-bonus-ridiculous-fishing-with-vlambeer/ App Store
iPad
iPhone
∧App∧Store
∧iPad
∧iPhone ]]></h>
 <alt><![CDATA[2,8,32,128]]></alt>
 <bodys><![CDATA[∧mobile∧platforms, ∧products, ∧tablet∧computers We've got one last bit of content on Ridiculous Fishing [$2.99] that we think you'll dig, even if you've been cranking away on its core play loop since the game hit last night. Below, is a TA Plays "Bonus" in which Rami and JW from Vlambeer join us for a quick session of the game. They drop some mad knowledge about its creation and mechanics, and do a decent bit of chiding over my inability to fish all that well. Even if you've read the reviews, checked out our latest podcast, or got swept up in the pre-release buzz, this is a video that's worth the watch since we've got two of the creators with us.
In case you didn't know, by the way, Ridiculous Fishing is insanely good. It's quirky in all the right ways and has an amazing amount of production value. From art, to sound, to controls, this thing sings on the iPhone and iPad. Give it a look if you haven't yet:
App Store Link: Ridiculous Fishing - A Tale of Redemption, $2.99 (Universal)]]></bodys>
 <bodyn><![CDATA[10101010]]></bodyn>
 <meta><![CDATA[1449]]></meta>
 <ref><![CDATA[94]]></ref>
 <url><![CDATA[http://api.snatz.com/index.php?app=asmapi&event=feeds&time=new&feed_id=15506518999820027524&item_id=17619488404212883200-13-03]]></url>
 <cdate>1376321299</cdate>
 <mmedia>0</mmedia>
 <bseo>0</bseo>
 <uid>2</uid>
 <sid>1</sid>
 <lang>255</lang>
 <afflags0>2,8,32,128</afflags0>
 <afflags1>30</afflags1>
 <afflags2>1</afflags2>
 <afflags3>2,8,32,128</afflags3>
 <afflags4>2,8,32,128</afflags4>
 <afflags5>2,8,32,128</afflags5>
 <afflags6>2,8,32,128</afflags6>
 <afflags7>2,8,32,128</afflags7>

 <afflags0ex>1,4,16,64</afflags0ex>
 <afflags1ex>1,4,16,64</afflags1ex>
 <afflags2ex>1,4,16,64</afflags2ex>
 <afflags3ex>1,4,16,64</afflags3ex>
 <afflags4ex>1,4,16,64</afflags4ex>
 <afflags5ex>1,4,16,64</afflags5ex>
 <afflags6ex>1,4,16,64</afflags6ex>
 <afflags7ex>1,4,16,64</afflags7ex>
</sphinx:document>
<sphinx:document id="9270227614923558010">
 <title><![CDATA[WWDC tickets go on sale April 25th, conference to be held June 10-14]]></title>
 <h><![CDATA[<a href='http://images.intomobile.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/04/wwdc650.jpg' target=_blank><img src='http://images.intomobile.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/04/wwdc650.jpg' title='size: 0 width: 0 height: 0'></a>Conference
Apple
sale
WWDC
announce
San Francisco
Moscone
∧Conference
∧Apple
∧sale
∧WWDC
∧announce
∧San∧Francisco
∧Moscone http://intomobile.com/2013/04/24/wwdc-tickets-go-sale-april-25th-conference-held-june-1014/ Apple
Conference
Jonathan Ive
San Francisco
WWDC
announce
design
iOS
∧Apple
∧Conference
∧Jonathan∧Ive
∧San∧Francisco
∧WWDC
∧announce
∧design
∧iOS ]]></h>
 <alt><![CDATA[2,8,32,128]]></alt>
 <bodys><![CDATA[∧cities∧by∧GDP, ∧companies, ∧design, ∧dic∧events, ∧it∧people, ∧mobile∧operating∧systems Apple announced today that its yearly Worldwide Developers Conference (WWDC) will kick off June 10 and go through June 14, It will be held at San Francisco’s Moscone West. Start preparing for the buying frenzy as tickets for WWDC 2013 go on sale starting Thursday, April 25 at 10 a.m. PDT. If previous years are any indication, tickets will sell out very quickly.
WWDC will be an exciting event for Apple fans. Apple is expected to unveil the next iteration of OS X and shed some light on iOS 7. This upcoming version iOS should rock some of the design influences of Jony Ive, who took over as lead of iOS development late last year.
[Via Apple]
WWDC tickets go on sale April 25th, conference to be held June 10-14 originally appeared on IntoMobile.com on 2013-04-24T13:14:21Z. FV1gMYsz9b5j]]></bodys>
 <bodyn><![CDATA[10101010]]></bodyn>
 <meta><![CDATA[1334]]></meta>
 <ref><![CDATA[93]]></ref>
 <url><![CDATA[http://api.snatz.com/index.php?app=asmapi&event=feeds&time=new&feed_id=17611317671334349533&item_id=10050006313463792724-13-04]]></url>
 <cdate>1376321299</cdate>
 <mmedia>0</mmedia>
 <bseo>0</bseo>
 <uid>2</uid>
 <sid>1</sid>
 <lang>255</lang>
 <afflags0>2,8,32,128</afflags0>
 <afflags1>30</afflags1>
 <afflags2>1</afflags2>
 <afflags3>2,8,32,128</afflags3>
 <afflags4>2,8,32,128</afflags4>
 <afflags5>2,8,32,128</afflags5>
 <afflags6>2,8,32,128</afflags6>
 <afflags7>2,8,32,128</afflags7>

 <afflags0ex>1,4,16,64</afflags0ex>
 <afflags1ex>1,4,16,64</afflags1ex>
 <afflags2ex>1,4,16,64</afflags2ex>
 <afflags3ex>1,4,16,64</afflags3ex>
 <afflags4ex>1,4,16,64</afflags4ex>
 <afflags5ex>1,4,16,64</afflags5ex>
 <afflags6ex>1,4,16,64</afflags6ex>
 <afflags7ex>1,4,16,64</afflags7ex>
</sphinx:document>
<sphinx:document id="9270231307696371353">
 <title><![CDATA[Congress looks to tighten e-mail privacy law]]></title>
 <h><![CDATA[law
Congress
∧law
∧Congress http://pcworld.com/article/262275/congress_looks_to_tighten_email_privacy_law.html#tk.rss_main law
∧law ]]></h>
 <alt><![CDATA[2,8,32,128]]></alt>
 <bodys><![CDATA[∧dic∧events A new bill will require warrants for authorities to access e-mail and other private online communications.]]></bodys>
 <bodyn><![CDATA[10101010]]></bodyn>
 <meta><![CDATA[611]]></meta>
 <ref><![CDATA[93]]></ref>
 <url><![CDATA[http://api.snatz.com/index.php?app=asmapi&event=feeds&time=new&feed_id=11783833855997627850&item_id=14498773249471978250-12-09]]></url>
 <cdate>1376321299</cdate>
 <mmedia>0</mmedia>
 <bseo>0</bseo>
 <uid>2</uid>
 <sid>1</sid>
 <lang>255</lang>
 <afflags0>2,8,32,128</afflags0>
 <afflags1>30</afflags1>
 <afflags2>1</afflags2>
 <afflags3>2,8,32,128</afflags3>
 <afflags4>2,8,32,128</afflags4>
 <afflags5>2,8,32,128</afflags5>
 <afflags6>2,8,32,128</afflags6>
 <afflags7>2,8,32,128</afflags7>

 <afflags0ex>1,4,16,64</afflags0ex>
 <afflags1ex>1,4,16,64</afflags1ex>
 <afflags2ex>1,4,16,64</afflags2ex>
 <afflags3ex>1,4,16,64</afflags3ex>
 <afflags4ex>1,4,16,64</afflags4ex>
 <afflags5ex>1,4,16,64</afflags5ex>
 <afflags6ex>1,4,16,64</afflags6ex>
 <afflags7ex>1,4,16,64</afflags7ex>
</sphinx:document>
<sphinx:document id="9270231879441531542">
 <title><![CDATA[Fifa 13 – review]]></title>
 <h><![CDATA[EA
PC
Wii
PS3
Fifa 13
Xbox 360
∧EA
∧PC
∧Wii
∧PS3
∧Fifa∧13
∧Xbox∧360 http://guardian.co.uk/technology/2012/oct/07/fifa-13-games-review EA
PS3
∧EA
∧PS3 ]]></h>
 <alt><![CDATA[2,8,32,128]]></alt>
 <bodys><![CDATA[∧companies, ∧products Xbox 360, PS3, Wii, PC, EA, cert 3The explosion of smartphone titles such as Flick Kick Football and New Star Soccer have made football games more accessible than ever, opening the genre to audiences likely to balk at the convoluted menus and realistic gameplay of Fifa. But for the full football experience, it is the latter that remains the best title on offer, and this year's edition maintains the&nbsp;pedigree.Fifa 13 offers a big step forward over its predecessor, with player stats that now reflect their real-life counterparts, vastly improved dribbling, better team-mate AI, and commentary that includes touchline reports and score updates. There's also a new score-based challenge mode, Skill Games, which is almost as addictive as the aforementioned smartphone titles.But the biggest change involves ball control. Players can no longer expect near-perfect first touches, and poor passes to average players may result in loss of control. It can be frustrating, but it also adds unpredictability and excitement to the gameplay.Fifa 13's depth and realism make it a more difficult title to pick up and play than its handheld rivals, but given time even players who may initially find its complexity daunting will discover one of the finest sports titles ever made.Sports gamesSimulation gamesGamesXboxPS3WiiPCChris Dringguardian.co.uk &copy; 2012 Guardian News and Media Limited or its affiliated companies. All rights reserved. | Use of this content is subject to our Terms & Conditions | More Feeds]]></bodys>
 <bodyn><![CDATA[10101010]]></bodyn>
 <meta><![CDATA[1959]]></meta>
 <ref><![CDATA[94]]></ref>
 <url><![CDATA[http://api.snatz.com/index.php?app=asmapi&event=feeds&time=new&feed_id=15734708125508751561&item_id=17446161305331125994-12-10]]></url>
 <cdate>1376321299</cdate>
 <mmedia>0</mmedia>
 <bseo>0</bseo>
 <uid>2</uid>
 <sid>1</sid>
 <lang>255</lang>
 <afflags0>2,8,32,128</afflags0>
 <afflags1>30</afflags1>
 <afflags2>18</afflags2>
 <afflags3>2,8,32,128</afflags3>
 <afflags4>2,8,32,128</afflags4>
 <afflags5>2,8,32,128</afflags5>
 <afflags6>2,8,32,128</afflags6>
 <afflags7>2,8,32,128</afflags7>

 <afflags0ex>1,4,16,64</afflags0ex>
 <afflags1ex>1,4,16,64</afflags1ex>
 <afflags2ex>1,4,16,64</afflags2ex>
 <afflags3ex>1,4,16,64</afflags3ex>
 <afflags4ex>1,4,16,64</afflags4ex>
 <afflags5ex>1,4,16,64</afflags5ex>
 <afflags6ex>1,4,16,64</afflags6ex>
 <afflags7ex>1,4,16,64</afflags7ex>
</sphinx:document>
<sphinx:document id="9270237202875495102">
 <title><![CDATA[Android 4.2.1 Pushed to The AOSP]]></title>
 <h><![CDATA[<a href='http://androidheadlines.com/wp-content/uploads/2012/11/Android-4.2-Jelly-Bean1.jpg' target=_blank><img src='http://androidheadlines.com/wp-content/uploads/2012/11/Android-4.2-Jelly-Bean1.jpg' title='size: 0 width: 0 height: 0'></a>AOSP
Android 4
∧AOSP
∧Android∧4 http://androidheadlines.com/2012/11/android-4-2-1-pushed-to-the-aosp.html Android
Android 4
Samsung
∧Android
∧Android∧4
∧Samsung ]]></h>
 <alt><![CDATA[2,8,32,128]]></alt>
 <bodys><![CDATA[∧companies, ∧mobile∧operating∧systems, ∧photographic∧equipment∧makers, ∧products Earlier today, Nexus devices were getting treated to a point release – 4.2.1 – to address the issue of December being missed out from the People app. It’s only a minor fix and has now been pushed to the AOSP. With the source code of the release being pushed into Open Source there’s a good chance that ROMs are going to follow quickly. Aside from the change to the People app there’s little different under the hood but, these point releases are what inch towards OEMs picking up the code and preparing it for updates on their devices. As always, Jean-Baptiste Queru has given the announcment and you can find it below:
The source code for 4.2.1 is being pushed into AOSP right now. This is a minor release on top of 4.2. The build number is JOP40D, the git tag is android-4.2.1_r1.
4.2.1 uses the same device-specific proprietary files as 4.2.
The factory images for the various devices will follow in the next few days.
JBQ
As always, not all of the code is available right now but, the following builds are available:
device/common/+/android-4.2.1_r1
device/asus/grouper/+/android-4.2.1_r1
device/asus/tilapia/+/android-4.2.1_r1
device/samsung/tuna/+/android-4.2.1_r1
device/samsung/toro/+/android-4.2.1_r1
device/samsung/toroplus/+/android-4.2.1_r1
device/samsung/maguro/+/android-4.2.1_r1
device/samsung/manta/+/android-4.2.1_r1
device/lge/mako/+/android-4.2.1_r1
Soon enough, there should be some updates to the few Android 4.2 ROMs that are out there and updates from manufacturers should start being worked on. This isn’t to say that we’ll see updates any time soon but, it’s these point releases that manufacturers pick up to build their updates from. So, I suppose it’s about that time we start betting which manufacturer will bring their Android 4.2.1 update first, my money is on Samsung, how about you?
[Source: Android Police]]]></bodys>
 <bodyn><![CDATA[10101010]]></bodyn>
 <meta><![CDATA[2341]]></meta>
 <ref><![CDATA[94]]></ref>
 <url><![CDATA[http://api.snatz.com/index.php?app=asmapi&event=feeds&time=new&feed_id=11679771447006036549&item_id=9700135874579579269-12-11]]></url>
 <cdate>1376321299</cdate>
 <mmedia>0</mmedia>
 <bseo>0</bseo>
 <uid>2</uid>
 <sid>1</sid>
 <lang>255</lang>
 <afflags0>2,8,32,128</afflags0>
 <afflags1>30</afflags1>
 <afflags2>1</afflags2>
 <afflags3>2,8,32,128</afflags3>
 <afflags4>2,8,32,128</afflags4>
 <afflags5>2,8,32,128</afflags5>
 <afflags6>2,8,32,128</afflags6>
 <afflags7>2,8,32,128</afflags7>

 <afflags0ex>1,4,16,64</afflags0ex>
 <afflags1ex>1,4,16,64</afflags1ex>
 <afflags2ex>1,4,16,64</afflags2ex>
 <afflags3ex>1,4,16,64</afflags3ex>
 <afflags4ex>1,4,16,64</afflags4ex>
 <afflags5ex>1,4,16,64</afflags5ex>
 <afflags6ex>1,4,16,64</afflags6ex>
 <afflags7ex>1,4,16,64</afflags7ex>
</sphinx:document>
<sphinx:document id="9270254518649876934">
 <title><![CDATA[The Inside Network Job Board: Toca Boca, Alibaba, BrightRoll and more]]></title>
 <h><![CDATA[Boca
Toca
Alibaba
BrightRoll
Inside Network
∧Boca
∧Toca
∧Alibaba
∧BrightRoll
∧Inside∧Network http://insidemobileapps.com/2012/10/27/the-inside-network-job-board-toca-boca-alibaba-brightroll-and-more/ Amazon
Inside Network
∧Amazon
∧Inside∧Network ]]></h>
 <alt><![CDATA[2,8,32,128]]></alt>
 <bodys><![CDATA[∧companies The Inside Network Job Board is dedicated to providing you with the best social media job opportunities across social and mobile application platforms. Here are this week’s highlights from the Inside Network Job Board, including positions at: Toca Boca, Alibaba, BrightRoll, and more.
AdColony
Account Executive, Publisher Acquisitions
Alibaba
Senior Marketing Manager- Social and Online Marketing
Amazon Game Studios
Game Designer, Amazon Game Studios
Applifier
Senior Director, iOS Developer Relations
Arooga
Game Designer
BrightRoll
AdOps Coordinator (NYC)
Account Manager
Marketing Assistant
Campaign Manager (NYC)
CyberCoders
Tech/Career Blogger (Freelance)
Games Cafe Inc.
Senior Flash Game Programmer
Game Programmer
UI/UX Designer/Artist
High 5 Games
Flash Developer
Social Media Analyst
Customer Support Manager
UI/UX Designer
Project Manager
JBA International – IT talent management
Business Development Executive
Kabam
Developer Relations Manager – Mobile
King.com
UX/UI Artist
Business Manager
Game Designer
Game Developer
Backend Java Developer
Product Manager (Producer) – Mobile
Pocket Gems
Game Systems Designer
Visual Designer
Scopely
Mobile Engineer
Game Designer
Platform Engineer
Social Point
Project Manager (iOS/Android)
Toca Boca
Marketing Coordinator
User Acquisition Manager
TrialPay
Mobile Partnership Development Executive
Wooga GmbH
Product Manager – Metrics
iOS Games Developer
Lead Artist – Arcade Mobile
&nbsp;
&nbsp;
&nbsp;
&nbsp;]]></bodys>
 <bodyn><![CDATA[10101010]]></bodyn>
 <meta><![CDATA[2073]]></meta>
 <ref><![CDATA[93]]></ref>
 <url><![CDATA[http://api.snatz.com/index.php?app=asmapi&event=feeds&time=new&feed_id=14092476423260344126&item_id=13163226288128970944-12-10]]></url>
 <cdate>1376321299</cdate>
 <mmedia>0</mmedia>
 <bseo>0</bseo>
 <uid>2</uid>
 <sid>1</sid>
 <lang>255</lang>
 <afflags0>1</afflags0>
 <afflags1>30</afflags1>
 <afflags2>18</afflags2>
 <afflags3>2,8,32,128</afflags3>
 <afflags4>2,8,32,128</afflags4>
 <afflags5>2,8,32,128</afflags5>
 <afflags6>2,8,32,128</afflags6>
 <afflags7>2,8,32,128</afflags7>

 <afflags0ex>1,4,16,64</afflags0ex>
 <afflags1ex>1,4,16,64</afflags1ex>
 <afflags2ex>1,4,16,64</afflags2ex>
 <afflags3ex>1,4,16,64</afflags3ex>
 <afflags4ex>1,4,16,64</afflags4ex>
 <afflags5ex>1,4,16,64</afflags5ex>
 <afflags6ex>1,4,16,64</afflags6ex>
 <afflags7ex>1,4,16,64</afflags7ex>
</sphinx:document>
<sphinx:document id="9270259295291605751">
 <title><![CDATA[Surface Pros oversleeping, refusing to wake up from sleep mode]]></title>
 <h><![CDATA[<a href='http://www.neowin.net/images/news/logos/2007833037surfacelogo_medium.jpg' target=_blank><img src='http://www.neowin.net/images/news/logos/2007833037surfacelogo_medium.jpg' title='size: 0 width: 0 height: 0'></a>sleep mode
Surface Pro
∧sleep∧mode
∧Surface∧Pro http://neowin.net/news/surface-pros-oversleeping-refusing-to-wake-up-from-sleep-mode Microsoft
Surface Pro
∧Microsoft
∧Surface∧Pro ]]></h>
 <alt><![CDATA[2,8,32,128]]></alt>
 <bodys><![CDATA[∧companies, ∧tablet∧computers Microsoft Surface Pro users have been unable to wake their devices from sleep mode. Microsoft have not yet acknowledged the issue, however forum users have found an easy fix. Read more...]]></bodys>
 <bodyn><![CDATA[10101010]]></bodyn>
 <meta><![CDATA[700]]></meta>
 <ref><![CDATA[94]]></ref>
 <url><![CDATA[http://api.snatz.com/index.php?app=asmapi&event=feeds&time=new&feed_id=12443878012998951940&item_id=10141413174635173574-13-03]]></url>
 <cdate>1376321299</cdate>
 <mmedia>0</mmedia>
 <bseo>0</bseo>
 <uid>2</uid>
 <sid>1</sid>
 <lang>255</lang>
 <afflags0>2,8,32,128</afflags0>
 <afflags1>30</afflags1>
 <afflags2>1</afflags2>
 <afflags3>2,8,32,128</afflags3>
 <afflags4>2,8,32,128</afflags4>
 <afflags5>2,8,32,128</afflags5>
 <afflags6>2,8,32,128</afflags6>
 <afflags7>2,8,32,128</afflags7>

 <afflags0ex>1,4,16,64</afflags0ex>
 <afflags1ex>1,4,16,64</afflags1ex>
 <afflags2ex>1,4,16,64</afflags2ex>
 <afflags3ex>1,4,16,64</afflags3ex>
 <afflags4ex>1,4,16,64</afflags4ex>
 <afflags5ex>1,4,16,64</afflags5ex>
 <afflags6ex>1,4,16,64</afflags6ex>
 <afflags7ex>1,4,16,64</afflags7ex>
</sphinx:document>
<sphinx:document id="9270260114494482460">
 <title><![CDATA[Dropbox doubles plan sizes; intros 500GB option]]></title>
 <h><![CDATA[Dropbox
∧Dropbox http://news.cnet.com/8301-1001_3-57469651-92/dropbox-doubles-plan-sizes-intros-500gb-option/?part=rss&subj=news&tag=title Dropbox
∧Dropbox ]]></h>
 <alt><![CDATA[2,8,32,128]]></alt>
 <bodys><![CDATA[∧file∧hosting∧services Need 500GB of cloud storage space just for your own files? Dropbox can do that now.
[Read more]]]></bodys>
 <bodyn><![CDATA[10101010]]></bodyn>
 <meta><![CDATA[630]]></meta>
 <ref><![CDATA[93]]></ref>
 <url><![CDATA[http://api.snatz.com/index.php?app=asmapi&event=feeds&time=new&feed_id=11221331071403660916&item_id=18095386694900504459-12-07]]></url>
 <cdate>1376321299</cdate>
 <mmedia>0</mmedia>
 <bseo>0</bseo>
 <uid>2</uid>
 <sid>1</sid>
 <lang>255</lang>
 <afflags0>2,8,32,128</afflags0>
 <afflags1>30</afflags1>
 <afflags2>18</afflags2>
 <afflags3>2,8,32,128</afflags3>
 <afflags4>2,8,32,128</afflags4>
 <afflags5>2,8,32,128</afflags5>
 <afflags6>2,8,32,128</afflags6>
 <afflags7>2,8,32,128</afflags7>

 <afflags0ex>1,4,16,64</afflags0ex>
 <afflags1ex>1,4,16,64</afflags1ex>
 <afflags2ex>1,4,16,64</afflags2ex>
 <afflags3ex>1,4,16,64</afflags3ex>
 <afflags4ex>1,4,16,64</afflags4ex>
 <afflags5ex>1,4,16,64</afflags5ex>
 <afflags6ex>1,4,16,64</afflags6ex>
 <afflags7ex>1,4,16,64</afflags7ex>
</sphinx:document>
<sphinx:document id="9270265164604139944">
 <title><![CDATA[All-new Jeep Cherokee vs. 2014 Range Rover Sport]]></title>
 <h><![CDATA[<a href='http://www.product-reviews.net/wp-content/uploads/All-new-Jeep-Cherokee-vs.-2014-Range-Rover-Sport-2-200x110.jpg' target=_blank><img src='http://www.product-reviews.net/wp-content/uploads/All-new-Jeep-Cherokee-vs.-2014-Range-Rover-Sport-2-200x110.jpg' title='size: 0 width: 0 height: 0'></a>Cherokee
Range Rover Sport
Land Rover
Chrysler
∧Cherokee
∧Range∧Rover∧Sport
∧Land∧Rover
∧Chrysler http://product-reviews.net/2013/03/27/all-new-jeep-cherokee-vs-2014-range-rover-sport/ Apple
New York City
design
∧Apple
∧New∧York∧City
∧design ]]></h>
 <alt><![CDATA[2,8,32,128]]></alt>
 <bodys><![CDATA[∧cities∧by∧GDP, ∧companies, ∧design Both Chrysler and Land Rover have been teasing us with one or two images of their all-new Jeep Cherokee and the 2014 Range Rover Sport just to get out juices going. However, almost hours ahead of the New York Auto Show both companies have treated us to a multitude of new photos, and we have to say they are looking rather special.
While the two models will compete in the same market, there’s no denying the all-new Range Rover Sport will be the most popular at the show, seeing as though this SUV is a popular choice with drivers in The Big Apple.
The 2014 Jeep Cherokee certainly looks as though it will try its best in a very competitive market, and looking at some of these images the exterior and interior, we have to say the design department has done an impressive job. There are front-wheel and all-wheel drive options, as well as a choice of a 2.4 liter and 3.2 liter engines, producing 184 and 271 horsepower respectively. Full details can be found here.
As for the 2014 Range Rover Sport it’s nice to see a true Range Rover, unlike the horrible Evoque, which looks as though it has been rolled on its roof. This all-new model has been reworked and as such has been on a bit of a diet, so now weighs 800 pounds less, and that’s even with the inclusion of a third row.
The engine options for the Sport makes the Cherokee look like child’s play, as you have a choice of a 3.0-liter supercharged V6 or a 5.0-liter supercharged V8, which produces 340 and 510 horsepower respectively. Full details can be found on the official Land Rover website.]]></bodys>
 <bodyn><![CDATA[10101010]]></bodyn>
 <meta><![CDATA[2053]]></meta>
 <ref><![CDATA[94]]></ref>
 <url><![CDATA[http://api.snatz.com/index.php?app=asmapi&event=feeds&time=new&feed_id=12906826684037423143&item_id=13549039557438212411-13-03]]></url>
 <cdate>1376321299</cdate>
 <mmedia>0</mmedia>
 <bseo>0</bseo>
 <uid>2</uid>
 <sid>1</sid>
 <lang>255</lang>
 <afflags0>2,8,32,128</afflags0>
 <afflags1>30</afflags1>
 <afflags2>1</afflags2>
 <afflags3>2,8,32,128</afflags3>
 <afflags4>2,8,32,128</afflags4>
 <afflags5>2,8,32,128</afflags5>
 <afflags6>2,8,32,128</afflags6>
 <afflags7>2,8,32,128</afflags7>

 <afflags0ex>1,4,16,64</afflags0ex>
 <afflags1ex>1,4,16,64</afflags1ex>
 <afflags2ex>1,4,16,64</afflags2ex>
 <afflags3ex>1,4,16,64</afflags3ex>
 <afflags4ex>1,4,16,64</afflags4ex>
 <afflags5ex>1,4,16,64</afflags5ex>
 <afflags6ex>1,4,16,64</afflags6ex>
 <afflags7ex>1,4,16,64</afflags7ex>
</sphinx:document>
<sphinx:document id="9270275869241325636">
 <title><![CDATA[Pano + Lomo + Graphy / A Community Diana F+ Event in Chile]]></title>
 <h><![CDATA[<a href='http://cloud.lomography.com/576/377/a6/43588f0e5d5a010917960428ecbbe5bae25721.jpg' target=_blank><img src='http://cloud.lomography.com/576/377/a6/43588f0e5d5a010917960428ecbbe5bae25721.jpg' title='size: 0 width: 0 height: 0'></a>Pano
Chile
Graphy
Community Diana F
Lomographic Embassy
∧Pano
∧Chile
∧Graphy
∧Community∧Diana∧F
∧Lomographic∧Embassy http://lomography.com/magazine/events/2012/09/12/pano-lomo-graphy-a-community-diana-f-plus-event-in-chile Chile
Holiday
LOMO
Santiago
Vimeo
∧Chile
∧Holiday
∧LOMO
∧Santiago
∧Vimeo ]]></h>
 <alt><![CDATA[2,8,32,128]]></alt>
 <bodys><![CDATA[∧cities∧by∧GDP, ∧countries, ∧dic∧events, ∧photographic∧equipment∧makers, ∧video∧hosting∧services The Lomographic Embassy in Chile proudly presents its first photo intervention project: the Pano + Lomo + Graphy. A two stage community action... come on in and take a look to the video of our project!
To browse this gallery please read this post on our website
Last August, Lomography Chile was working on a secret project to be part of the 2nd anniversary of one of the biggest and most important cultural center in Santiago: Centro Gabriela Mistral (aka GAM).
In an open call, 10 Lomographers and their Diana F+ where invited to be part of this event. The goal: to make a big panorama of GAM using Analogue techniques.
In the first stage, we met to shoot the facade and the central patio with our plastic cameras and some 800 Lomography Film as the area to be photographed didn´t receive direct light. We even had to push some films for the darker spots!
Later, with all the rolls processed, we made a selection of 112 shots that would be used to give life to this huge panorama!
Finally, to build up this exhibition we used the “band poster” thechnique. We printed all the pictures in 70 × 70 cms and stuck them to a big wall with wheat paste. After 6 hours of work and 20 liters of wheat paste, our analogue present was done!
We loved this project, especially the production of it as it perfectly resumes the analogue experience in photography of not really knowing what will be the final outcome, and having a dose of classic “lovable errors” like double exposure, light leaks, etc.
Thanks to all those who helped in making this project come true: Centro Cultural GAM, the Diana team, the Harinaguas team and the film team (Clickr) // Coca, Peropero, Gabriela Castro, Macarena Becas, Fram, Iaki, Paloma Mas, Javier Díaz, Felipe Cáceres, Tam, Alfredo Peñaloza, Sabino Aguad, Lomochile, Vania Contreras y Zeube.
If you like this project, share the video and spread the analogue love :)
Pano + Lomo + Grafía from Lomo Chile on Vimeo.
Lomography Chile
The Diana F+ is a new twist on the ‘60s classic cult camera. Famous for its dreamy and soft-focused images, the Diana F+ is now packed with extra features such as panorama and pinhole capabilities. Available in our Online Shop.
The Lomography Color Negative 120 800 ISO film is a high-speed medium-format film designed to bring a burst of vibrant color, as well as great saturation and contrast, in all lighting conditions! Shoot in bright sunshine, grey days, indoors or at night with a flash. See our selection of Lomography films here.]]></bodys>
 <bodyn><![CDATA[10101010]]></bodyn>
 <meta><![CDATA[3040]]></meta>
 <ref><![CDATA[94]]></ref>
 <url><![CDATA[http://api.snatz.com/index.php?app=asmapi&event=feeds&time=new&feed_id=12794359493175214647&item_id=17613654729368957217-12-09]]></url>
 <cdate>1376321299</cdate>
 <mmedia>0</mmedia>
 <bseo>0</bseo>
 <uid>2</uid>
 <sid>1</sid>
 <lang>255</lang>
 <afflags0>2,8,32,128</afflags0>
 <afflags1>30</afflags1>
 <afflags2>1</afflags2>
 <afflags3>2,8,32,128</afflags3>
 <afflags4>2,8,32,128</afflags4>
 <afflags5>2,8,32,128</afflags5>
 <afflags6>2,8,32,128</afflags6>
 <afflags7>2,8,32,128</afflags7>

 <afflags0ex>1,4,16,64</afflags0ex>
 <afflags1ex>1,4,16,64</afflags1ex>
 <afflags2ex>1,4,16,64</afflags2ex>
 <afflags3ex>1,4,16,64</afflags3ex>
 <afflags4ex>1,4,16,64</afflags4ex>
 <afflags5ex>1,4,16,64</afflags5ex>
 <afflags6ex>1,4,16,64</afflags6ex>
 <afflags7ex>1,4,16,64</afflags7ex>
</sphinx:document>
<sphinx:document id="9270304444852852195">
 <title><![CDATA[The cybernetic devices of Mobile World Congress (pictures)]]></title>
 <h><![CDATA[<a href='http://i.i.com.com/cnwk.1d/i/tim/2013/02/27/015MioAlphaWatch_35624754_700x500.jpg' target=_blank><img src='http://i.i.com.com/cnwk.1d/i/tim/2013/02/27/015MioAlphaWatch_35624754_700x500.jpg' title='size: 0 width: 0 height: 0'></a>measure heart rate
watch
Barcelona
Spain--The
Mobile World Congress
device
Alpha
Android
∧measure∧heart∧rate
∧watch
∧Barcelona
∧Spain∧∧The
∧Mobile∧World∧Congress
∧device
∧Alpha
∧Android http://reviews.cnet.com/2300-13970_7-10015990.html?part=rss&subj=cnet&tag=title Android
Barcelona
Mobile World Congress
∧Android
∧Barcelona
∧Mobile∧World∧Congress ]]></h>
 <alt><![CDATA[2,8,32,128]]></alt>
 <bodys><![CDATA[∧cities∧by∧GDP, ∧dic∧events, ∧mobile∧operating∧systems, ∧products Ranging from watches that talk to smartphones wirelessly and measure heart rate, to wearable computers running Android, MWC 2013 was replete with devices blurring the line between man and machine.BARCELONA, Spain--The Mio Alpha can monitor your heart rate, sync data to smartphone apps, and track when you're in your optimal exercise range. [Read more]]]></bodys>
 <bodyn><![CDATA[10101010]]></bodyn>
 <meta><![CDATA[856]]></meta>
 <ref><![CDATA[93]]></ref>
 <url><![CDATA[http://api.snatz.com/index.php?app=asmapi&event=feeds&time=new&feed_id=14983113245415276988&item_id=11035174629596888729-13-02]]></url>
 <cdate>1376321299</cdate>
 <mmedia>0</mmedia>
 <bseo>0</bseo>
 <uid>2</uid>
 <sid>1</sid>
 <lang>255</lang>
 <afflags0>1</afflags0>
 <afflags1>30</afflags1>
 <afflags2>18</afflags2>
 <afflags3>2,8,32,128</afflags3>
 <afflags4>2,8,32,128</afflags4>
 <afflags5>2,8,32,128</afflags5>
 <afflags6>2,8,32,128</afflags6>
 <afflags7>2,8,32,128</afflags7>

 <afflags0ex>1,4,16,64</afflags0ex>
 <afflags1ex>1,4,16,64</afflags1ex>
 <afflags2ex>1,4,16,64</afflags2ex>
 <afflags3ex>1,4,16,64</afflags3ex>
 <afflags4ex>1,4,16,64</afflags4ex>
 <afflags5ex>1,4,16,64</afflags5ex>
 <afflags6ex>1,4,16,64</afflags6ex>
 <afflags7ex>1,4,16,64</afflags7ex>
</sphinx:document>
<sphinx:document id="9270314098041398641">
 <title><![CDATA[Best Buy Nokia Lumia 920 pre-order page down? No problem]]></title>
 <h><![CDATA[<a href='http://wmpoweruser.com/wp-content/uploads/2012/10/HTC-8X-Nokia-Lumai-920-Pre-Order-620x216.jpg' target=_blank><img src='http://wmpoweruser.com/wp-content/uploads/2012/10/HTC-8X-Nokia-Lumai-920-Pre-Order-620x216.jpg' title='size: 0 width: 0 height: 0'></a>HTC
AT&T
Best Buy
Nokia Lumia
∧HTC
∧AT∧T
∧Best∧Buy
∧Nokia∧Lumia http://wmpoweruser.com/best-buy-nokia-lumia-920-pre-order-page-down-no-problem/ AT&T
Best Buy
HTC
Nokia Lumia
∧AT∧T
∧Best∧Buy
∧HTC
∧Nokia∧Lumia ]]></h>
 <alt><![CDATA[2,8,32,128]]></alt>
 <bodys><![CDATA[∧companies, ∧laptop∧brands∧and∧manufacturers, ∧products Best Buy briefly had, then pulled the pre-order page for the Nokia Lumia 920 and HTC 8X or AT&amp;T, likely because they were not meant to have revealed the prices of the still secretive handsets.
NokiaPoweruser has however managed to track down the individual links to the pages, meaning you can still get your pre-order in before the stampede starts.
The links are: Black, Cyan, Yellow and Red AT&amp;T Lumia 920.
Pre-order link Red
Pre-order Link Cyan
Pre-order Link Yellow
Pre-order Link Black
Via NokiaPoweruser.com  
googletag.defineSlot('/17729662/wmpoweruser/tech/gadget', [[300,250]], 'div-wmp-300-250-body-body2-hp').setTargeting('site',['wmp']).setTargeting('pos',['body']).setTargeting('place',['body2']).setTargeting('page',['site']).addService(googletag.pubads());
googletag.pubads().enableSyncRendering();
googletag.enableServices();
googletag.display('div-wmp-300-250-body-body2-hp']]></bodys>
 <bodyn><![CDATA[10101010]]></bodyn>
 <meta><![CDATA[1407]]></meta>
 <ref><![CDATA[93]]></ref>
 <url><![CDATA[http://api.snatz.com/index.php?app=asmapi&event=feeds&time=new&feed_id=12239875025132363884&item_id=15358021803736535416-12-10]]></url>
 <cdate>1376321299</cdate>
 <mmedia>0</mmedia>
 <bseo>0</bseo>
 <uid>2</uid>
 <sid>1</sid>
 <lang>255</lang>
 <afflags0>2</afflags0>
 <afflags1>30</afflags1>
 <afflags2>1</afflags2>
 <afflags3>2,8,32,128</afflags3>
 <afflags4>2,8,32,128</afflags4>
 <afflags5>2,8,32,128</afflags5>
 <afflags6>2,8,32,128</afflags6>
 <afflags7>2,8,32,128</afflags7>

 <afflags0ex>1,4,16,64</afflags0ex>
 <afflags1ex>1,4,16,64</afflags1ex>
 <afflags2ex>1,4,16,64</afflags2ex>
 <afflags3ex>1,4,16,64</afflags3ex>
 <afflags4ex>1,4,16,64</afflags4ex>
 <afflags5ex>1,4,16,64</afflags5ex>
 <afflags6ex>1,4,16,64</afflags6ex>
 <afflags7ex>1,4,16,64</afflags7ex>
</sphinx:document>
<sphinx:document id="9270317038483236901">
 <title><![CDATA[iPad Lunch Tray Brings TV Dinners Into The 21st Century]]></title>
 <h><![CDATA[<a href='http://cdn.cultofmac.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/04/1366274787.jpg' target=_blank><img src='http://cdn.cultofmac.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/04/1366274787.jpg' title='size: 0 width: 0 height: 0'></a>iPad
Kikkerland
Tray
∧iPad
∧Kikkerland
∧Tray http://cultofmac.com/224007/ipad-lunch-tray-brings-tv-dinners-into-the-21st-century/ Amazon
iPad
∧Amazon
∧iPad ]]></h>
 <alt><![CDATA[2,8,32,128]]></alt>
 <bodys><![CDATA[∧companies, ∧tablet∧computers Despite its obvious problems, it’s hard not to love this little iPad lap desk from Kikkerland. It’s not just that it would look so cute perched on your thighs with a snack and a suitable beverage, but that somebody thought to update the TV dinner for the internet age. The iPad Bed is just $13 (currently sold out at Kikkerland but available elsewhere: try Amazon), and sits firmly on your lap thanks to a cushioned base. The slot at the back holds the iPad in horizontal or vertical orientations, and the flat surface is the perfect place to stow hot liquids while you… Wait a second. The iPad is pretty splash-proof, as I have discovered after extensive use in the kitchen and bedroom, but even I’d balk at sitting a hot cup of coffee on a surface right next to my $800 tablet, especially as that tray-table is supported by my untrustworthy and wobble-prone lap. Also: coffee with a bagel? Coffee should never be drank with savory foods. That’s just disgusting. Still, I’m sold. I use the iPad in bed enough that this could even be considered a tax write-off. Source: Kikkerland Related StoriesAuxo App Switcher Coming To The iPad Next Month [Jailbreak]Sneak Peek Of Photoshop’s New Shake Reduction ToolLinkedIn Launches Redesigned Apps For Android & iOSGorgeous Intimo MacBook Desk Not Just For SecretariesPocket Improves Sharing And Highlighting&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;]]></bodys>
 <bodyn><![CDATA[10101010]]></bodyn>
 <meta><![CDATA[1889]]></meta>
 <ref><![CDATA[94]]></ref>
 <url><![CDATA[http://api.snatz.com/index.php?app=asmapi&event=feeds&time=new&feed_id=10472965104111650242&item_id=13299202925942326563-13-04]]></url>
 <cdate>1376321299</cdate>
 <mmedia>0</mmedia>
 <bseo>0</bseo>
 <uid>2</uid>
 <sid>1</sid>
 <lang>255</lang>
 <afflags0>1</afflags0>
 <afflags1>30</afflags1>
 <afflags2>18</afflags2>
 <afflags3>2,8,32,128</afflags3>
 <afflags4>2,8,32,128</afflags4>
 <afflags5>2,8,32,128</afflags5>
 <afflags6>2,8,32,128</afflags6>
 <afflags7>2,8,32,128</afflags7>

 <afflags0ex>1,4,16,64</afflags0ex>
 <afflags1ex>1,4,16,64</afflags1ex>
 <afflags2ex>1,4,16,64</afflags2ex>
 <afflags3ex>1,4,16,64</afflags3ex>
 <afflags4ex>1,4,16,64</afflags4ex>
 <afflags5ex>1,4,16,64</afflags5ex>
 <afflags6ex>1,4,16,64</afflags6ex>
 <afflags7ex>1,4,16,64</afflags7ex>
</sphinx:document>
<sphinx:document id="9270330831866517019">
 <title><![CDATA[5 great Google sites for teachers]]></title>
 <h><![CDATA[<a href='http://i.telegraph.co.uk/multimedia/archive/01369/Untitled-1_1369669c.jpg?__SQUARESPACE_CACHEVERSION=1349865408966' target=_blank><img src='http://i.telegraph.co.uk/multimedia/archive/01369/Untitled-1_1369669c.jpg?__SQUARESPACE_CACHEVERSION=1349865408966' title='size: 0 width: 0 height: 0'></a>Google Sites
∧Google∧Sites http://edgalaxy.com/journal/2012/10/10/5-great-google-sites-for-teachers.html Google
Google Maps
Google Sites
∧Google
∧Google∧Maps
∧Google∧Sites ]]></h>
 <alt><![CDATA[2,8,32,128]]></alt>
 <bodys><![CDATA[∧companies, ∧file∧hosting∧services, ∧search∧engines, ∧web∧map∧services Google has a number of web services and tools that offer a range of use to teachers.&nbsp; Here are five sites from the big G that you can use in you classroom today with some ideas to support them.
Google Custom Search Engine: Create your own class custom search engine and tell Google which sites you want it to index, and you&rsquo;ll be able to offer your students the best of the web.&nbsp; Ie:&nbsp; Create a science search engine inclusive of 10 of your favourite science sites.
Google Book Search: Search from a mammoth selection of&nbsp; books ranging from popular best sellers to out-of-print books on Google&rsquo;s Book Search.
Google classroom posters: When you have exhausted our awesome collection of classroom posters then,&nbsp; help your students search the web better with these posters that contain tips for using Google Search and other Google products.
Google classroom activities: Here, Google offers a small selection of activity ideas for primary school children.
Google Maps: Get your class to use Google Maps to build maps of your community, learn about cities, and more and now you can even explore the great barrier reef with street view too.
Please be sure to let us know about another great Google sites or tools you might use too.]]></bodys>
 <bodyn><![CDATA[10101010]]></bodyn>
 <meta><![CDATA[1743]]></meta>
 <ref><![CDATA[94]]></ref>
 <url><![CDATA[http://api.snatz.com/index.php?app=asmapi&event=feeds&time=new&feed_id=9725000368541804120&item_id=10466129993383222475-12-10]]></url>
 <cdate>1376321299</cdate>
 <mmedia>0</mmedia>
 <bseo>0</bseo>
 <uid>2</uid>
 <sid>1</sid>
 <lang>255</lang>
 <afflags0>2,8,32,128</afflags0>
 <afflags1>30</afflags1>
 <afflags2>1</afflags2>
 <afflags3>2,8,32,128</afflags3>
 <afflags4>2,8,32,128</afflags4>
 <afflags5>2,8,32,128</afflags5>
 <afflags6>2,8,32,128</afflags6>
 <afflags7>2,8,32,128</afflags7>

 <afflags0ex>1,4,16,64</afflags0ex>
 <afflags1ex>1,4,16,64</afflags1ex>
 <afflags2ex>1,4,16,64</afflags2ex>
 <afflags3ex>1,4,16,64</afflags3ex>
 <afflags4ex>1,4,16,64</afflags4ex>
 <afflags5ex>1,4,16,64</afflags5ex>
 <afflags6ex>1,4,16,64</afflags6ex>
 <afflags7ex>1,4,16,64</afflags7ex>
</sphinx:document>
<sphinx:document id="9270338890747921252">
 <title><![CDATA[3 ways your website should be working for you]]></title>
 <h><![CDATA[<a href='http://next.inman.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/03/photodune-2806465-online-internet-marketing-xs.jpg' target=_blank><img src='http://next.inman.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/03/photodune-2806465-online-internet-marketing-xs.jpg' title='size: 0 width: 0 height: 0'></a>website
computer screen
way
∧website
∧computer∧screen
∧way http://next.inman.com/2013/03/3-ways-your-website-should-be-working-for-you/ Google
Google Analytics
∧Google
∧Google∧Analytics ]]></h>
 <alt><![CDATA[2,8,32,128]]></alt>
 <bodys><![CDATA[∧applications, ∧companies, ∧search∧engines Whether you’re new to online marketing or you’ve had a website for years, making your website work for you, even when you’re not working on it directly, is a great way to continue spinning the online marketing wheels long after you’ve left the computer screen. Setting up a website to be properly optimized from the beginning is sometimes a lot easier than trying to fix an old website that has had issues in the past. Even working with an aged domain may not be effective if the site it’s been attached to is swimming in errors. The first place you need to start is to determine which is the best direction; start fresh with a new website and domain, try to fix the old one, or attach the mature domain to a new website.
Start with a solid foundation.
It doesn’t matter how beautifully staged the inside of the house may be, if the foundation is crumbling and the roof is about to cave in, there’s no point in dressing up the inside. Make sure your domain (URL) is not piggybacking on any other websites. If you can get to the homepage from a variety of different URL variations, Google will have a hard time figuring out which page is the actual website.
For instance; if you purchased the domain www.youwebsite.com yet your brokerage or MLS provider requires you use their web host or is simply a cheaper website, be sure that they don’t attach their name to the website as in www.yourwebsite.ourbrokerage.com you will also want to make sure there’s no additional codes after the URL such as www.yourwebsite.com/home or www.yourwebsite.com/home.php?.
The best way to determine this is to click on the link from your brokerage’s website, check the link once you are on your website by clicking the home button, or just trying a variety of URLs. If you can get to the homepage with the same content through any other way but your basic domain, www.yourwebsite.com, Google may see several copies of your home page on different domain URLs. This alone can hinder your rankings from the beginning. At this point it may be better to start fresh with a new domain and a new website than trying to repair and redirect all of the existing URLs.
Create content that is custom, unique, and searchable.
When you start to build your website make sure that every title, description, tags (if applicable), and keywords are intentional and purposeful, specifically talking about what your article is about. You don’t need to bold keywords or keep a high density of keywords in the content itself so long as you are writing quality content that is unique (never been talked about before in this exact manner) and on topics that someone would be looking for.
Cover more ground for leads by writing blog posts and pages about specific neighborhoods and styles of homes within those neighborhoods, events and activities from your perspective, market reports that are titled with the detailed month and year you’re focusing on, and answers to questions buyers and sellers may have. More people tend to research answers to questions than simply the information on a topic.
Keep readers on your site as long as possible.
If you’ve done the first two basic steps, the final step should be keeping those readers on your website as long as you can. Check your Google analytics and make sure that people are staying on your site at least 3 to 5 minutes or longer. If your bounce rate is over 40%, try to find a way to keep people on your site by offering more information that links to additional information. If you’re talking about selling a home in a particular neighborhood, provide links and teaser tags to other information on your site such as staging tips, pricing strategies, and getting the home sold quickly. This leads the reader from one article to another and before they realize it, they have viewed 5 to 10 pages on your website and have stayed 15 to 20 minutes. Google monitors this and ranks the site according to the user experience.
By completing these three simple tasks and setting up your website properly, it will work long after you’ve left the desk. People will continue to find your articles, your blog posts and your information, stay on your site longer, and eventually contact you directly.]]></bodys>
 <bodyn><![CDATA[10101010]]></bodyn>
 <meta><![CDATA[4728]]></meta>
 <ref><![CDATA[93]]></ref>
 <url><![CDATA[http://api.snatz.com/index.php?app=asmapi&event=feeds&time=new&feed_id=12287267935839624478&item_id=9822457754713983973-13-03]]></url>
 <cdate>1376321299</cdate>
 <mmedia>0</mmedia>
 <bseo>0</bseo>
 <uid>2</uid>
 <sid>1</sid>
 <lang>255</lang>
 <afflags0>2,8,32,128</afflags0>
 <afflags1>30</afflags1>
 <afflags2>1</afflags2>
 <afflags3>2,8,32,128</afflags3>
 <afflags4>2,8,32,128</afflags4>
 <afflags5>2,8,32,128</afflags5>
 <afflags6>2,8,32,128</afflags6>
 <afflags7>2,8,32,128</afflags7>

 <afflags0ex>1,4,16,64</afflags0ex>
 <afflags1ex>1,4,16,64</afflags1ex>
 <afflags2ex>1,4,16,64</afflags2ex>
 <afflags3ex>1,4,16,64</afflags3ex>
 <afflags4ex>1,4,16,64</afflags4ex>
 <afflags5ex>1,4,16,64</afflags5ex>
 <afflags6ex>1,4,16,64</afflags6ex>
 <afflags7ex>1,4,16,64</afflags7ex>
</sphinx:document>
<sphinx:document id="9270378981962523820">
 <title><![CDATA[Vote: New Entries for Friday 5.17.13 — Small Cool Contest]]></title>
 <h><![CDATA[<a href='http://g-ec1.apartmenttherapy.com/3992847/Sebastian-5b627140001fd._w.540__rect540.jpeg' target=_blank><img src='http://g-ec1.apartmenttherapy.com/3992847/Sebastian-5b627140001fd._w.540__rect540.jpeg' title='size: 0 width: 0 height: 0'></a>home
Cool Contest
∧home
∧Cool∧Contest http://apartmenttherapy.com/vote-new-entries-for-friday-51713-small-cool-contest-189569 ]]></h>
 <alt><![CDATA[2,8,32,128]]></alt>
 <bodys><![CDATA[Who has the smallest coolest home? It's up to you to decide. Click through to check out today's entries and then vote for your favorites. International: Sebastian's Multipurpose Space Teeny-Tiny: Shari's Airstream Studio Tiny: Jason's Luxe Factor International: Matthew's Nothing Else Like It Little: Carly's Converted Warehouse Tiny: Luz's Lucky Location Tiny: Alana's Gut Renovation Teeny-Tiny: Leslie's Enchanting Sunlight More&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;]]></bodys>
 <bodyn><![CDATA[10101010]]></bodyn>
 <meta><![CDATA[984]]></meta>
 <ref><![CDATA[94]]></ref>
 <url><![CDATA[http://api.snatz.com/index.php?app=asmapi&event=feeds&time=new&feed_id=16433223293408295632&item_id=11016367141037121708-13-05]]></url>
 <cdate>1376321299</cdate>
 <mmedia>0</mmedia>
 <bseo>0</bseo>
 <uid>2</uid>
 <sid>1</sid>
 <lang>255</lang>
 <afflags0>2,8,32,128</afflags0>
 <afflags1>24</afflags1>
 <afflags2>18</afflags2>
 <afflags3>2,8,32,128</afflags3>
 <afflags4>2,8,32,128</afflags4>
 <afflags5>2,8,32,128</afflags5>
 <afflags6>2,8,32,128</afflags6>
 <afflags7>2,8,32,128</afflags7>

 <afflags0ex>1,4,16,64</afflags0ex>
 <afflags1ex>1,4,16,64</afflags1ex>
 <afflags2ex>1,4,16,64</afflags2ex>
 <afflags3ex>1,4,16,64</afflags3ex>
 <afflags4ex>1,4,16,64</afflags4ex>
 <afflags5ex>1,4,16,64</afflags5ex>
 <afflags6ex>1,4,16,64</afflags6ex>
 <afflags7ex>1,4,16,64</afflags7ex>
</sphinx:document>
<sphinx:document id="9270405665377791069">
 <title><![CDATA[Nikon D7100 announced for India, starts at Rs. 79,450]]></title>
 <h><![CDATA[D7000 DSLR
D7100
India
Nikon
announce
successor
∧D7000∧DSLR
∧D7100
∧India
∧Nikon
∧announce
∧successor http://gigjets.com/02/nikon-d7100-announced-for-india-starts-at-rs-79450/ India
Nikon
announce
∧India
∧Nikon
∧announce ]]></h>
 <alt><![CDATA[2,8,32,128]]></alt>
 <bodys><![CDATA[∧countries, ∧dic∧events, ∧photographic∧equipment∧makers The successor to the Nikon D7000 DSLR has arrived in the Indian market and it ...]]></bodys>
 <bodyn><![CDATA[10101010]]></bodyn>
 <meta><![CDATA[574]]></meta>
 <ref><![CDATA[94]]></ref>
 <url><![CDATA[http://api.snatz.com/index.php?app=asmapi&event=feeds&time=new&feed_id=13224934693203429433&item_id=10044495927923965441-13-02]]></url>
 <cdate>1376321299</cdate>
 <mmedia>0</mmedia>
 <bseo>0</bseo>
 <uid>2</uid>
 <sid>1</sid>
 <lang>255</lang>
 <afflags0>2,8,32,128</afflags0>
 <afflags1>30</afflags1>
 <afflags2>1</afflags2>
 <afflags3>2,8,32,128</afflags3>
 <afflags4>2,8,32,128</afflags4>
 <afflags5>2,8,32,128</afflags5>
 <afflags6>2,8,32,128</afflags6>
 <afflags7>2,8,32,128</afflags7>

 <afflags0ex>1,4,16,64</afflags0ex>
 <afflags1ex>1,4,16,64</afflags1ex>
 <afflags2ex>1,4,16,64</afflags2ex>
 <afflags3ex>1,4,16,64</afflags3ex>
 <afflags4ex>1,4,16,64</afflags4ex>
 <afflags5ex>1,4,16,64</afflags5ex>
 <afflags6ex>1,4,16,64</afflags6ex>
 <afflags7ex>1,4,16,64</afflags7ex>
</sphinx:document>
<sphinx:document id="9270423387564246896">
 <title><![CDATA[Google announces new Nexus tablets, smartphone]]></title>
 <h><![CDATA[Google
announce
New York City
∧Google
∧announce
∧New∧York∧City http://news.cnet.com/8301-1023_3-57542063-93/google-announces-new-nexus-tablets-smartphone/?part=rss&subj=news&tag=title Google
New York City
announce
∧Google
∧New∧York∧City
∧announce ]]></h>
 <alt><![CDATA[2,8,32,128]]></alt>
 <bodys><![CDATA[∧cities∧by∧GDP, ∧companies, ∧dic∧events, ∧search∧engines In lieu of New York event, Google makes a series of big announcements via blog post. [Read more]]]></bodys>
 <bodyn><![CDATA[10101010]]></bodyn>
 <meta><![CDATA[629]]></meta>
 <ref><![CDATA[94]]></ref>
 <url><![CDATA[http://api.snatz.com/index.php?app=asmapi&event=feeds&time=new&feed_id=11221331071403660916&item_id=11582205864170670146-12-10]]></url>
 <cdate>1376321299</cdate>
 <mmedia>0</mmedia>
 <bseo>0</bseo>
 <uid>2</uid>
 <sid>1</sid>
 <lang>255</lang>
 <afflags0>1</afflags0>
 <afflags1>30</afflags1>
 <afflags2>18</afflags2>
 <afflags3>2,8,32,128</afflags3>
 <afflags4>2,8,32,128</afflags4>
 <afflags5>2,8,32,128</afflags5>
 <afflags6>2,8,32,128</afflags6>
 <afflags7>2,8,32,128</afflags7>

 <afflags0ex>1,4,16,64</afflags0ex>
 <afflags1ex>1,4,16,64</afflags1ex>
 <afflags2ex>1,4,16,64</afflags2ex>
 <afflags3ex>1,4,16,64</afflags3ex>
 <afflags4ex>1,4,16,64</afflags4ex>
 <afflags5ex>1,4,16,64</afflags5ex>
 <afflags6ex>1,4,16,64</afflags6ex>
 <afflags7ex>1,4,16,64</afflags7ex>
</sphinx:document>
<sphinx:document id="9270432653415792644">
 <title><![CDATA[A Firefox Smartphone for the Developing World]]></title>
 <h><![CDATA[Firefox
Smartphone
∧Firefox
∧Smartphone http://bits.blogs.nytimes.com/2012/09/07/a-firefox-smartphone-for-the-poor/ America
Firefox
iPhone
∧America
∧Firefox
∧iPhone ]]></h>
 <alt><![CDATA[2,8,32,128]]></alt>
 <bodys><![CDATA[∧countries, ∧products, ∧web∧browsers The foundation that oversees Firefox says it will have a smartphone operating system on the market in early 2013. The phone is expected to cost one-sixth that of an iPhone. The first market is Latin America, then the rest of the developing world.]]></bodys>
 <bodyn><![CDATA[10101010]]></bodyn>
 <meta><![CDATA[733]]></meta>
 <ref><![CDATA[94]]></ref>
 <url><![CDATA[http://api.snatz.com/index.php?app=asmapi&event=feeds&time=new&feed_id=17497262061122939910&item_id=10166438447251200287-12-09]]></url>
 <cdate>1376321299</cdate>
 <mmedia>0</mmedia>
 <bseo>0</bseo>
 <uid>2</uid>
 <sid>1</sid>
 <lang>255</lang>
 <afflags0>12</afflags0>
 <afflags1>30</afflags1>
 <afflags2>18</afflags2>
 <afflags3>2,8,32,128</afflags3>
 <afflags4>2,8,32,128</afflags4>
 <afflags5>2,8,32,128</afflags5>
 <afflags6>2,8,32,128</afflags6>
 <afflags7>2,8,32,128</afflags7>

 <afflags0ex>1,4,16,64</afflags0ex>
 <afflags1ex>1,4,16,64</afflags1ex>
 <afflags2ex>1,4,16,64</afflags2ex>
 <afflags3ex>1,4,16,64</afflags3ex>
 <afflags4ex>1,4,16,64</afflags4ex>
 <afflags5ex>1,4,16,64</afflags5ex>
 <afflags6ex>1,4,16,64</afflags6ex>
 <afflags7ex>1,4,16,64</afflags7ex>
</sphinx:document>
<sphinx:document id="9270441005162566291">
 <title><![CDATA[Raspberry Pi grows an eye]]></title>
 <h><![CDATA[PiCam
Sunny
Raspberry Pi
∧PiCam
∧Sunny
∧Raspberry∧Pi http://theregister.co.uk/2013/02/07/raspberry_pi_camera_module_revealed/ Raspberry Pi
∧Raspberry∧Pi ]]></h>
 <alt><![CDATA[2,8,32,128]]></alt>
 <bodys><![CDATA[∧products Snaps suggest Chinese cams-for-mobes-maker Sunny will supply $25 PiCam The Raspberry Pi Foundation has released photos of a forthcoming camera module for the popular single-board computer.]]></bodys>
 <bodyn><![CDATA[10101010]]></bodyn>
 <meta><![CDATA[655]]></meta>
 <ref><![CDATA[94]]></ref>
 <url><![CDATA[http://api.snatz.com/index.php?app=asmapi&event=feeds&time=new&feed_id=17473413645308128375&item_id=12877939007542184470-13-02]]></url>
 <cdate>1376321299</cdate>
 <mmedia>0</mmedia>
 <bseo>0</bseo>
 <uid>2</uid>
 <sid>1</sid>
 <lang>255</lang>
 <afflags0>1</afflags0>
 <afflags1>30</afflags1>
 <afflags2>18</afflags2>
 <afflags3>2,8,32,128</afflags3>
 <afflags4>2,8,32,128</afflags4>
 <afflags5>2,8,32,128</afflags5>
 <afflags6>2,8,32,128</afflags6>
 <afflags7>2,8,32,128</afflags7>

 <afflags0ex>1,4,16,64</afflags0ex>
 <afflags1ex>1,4,16,64</afflags1ex>
 <afflags2ex>1,4,16,64</afflags2ex>
 <afflags3ex>1,4,16,64</afflags3ex>
 <afflags4ex>1,4,16,64</afflags4ex>
 <afflags5ex>1,4,16,64</afflags5ex>
 <afflags6ex>1,4,16,64</afflags6ex>
 <afflags7ex>1,4,16,64</afflags7ex>
</sphinx:document>
<sphinx:document id="9270465217260087132">
 <title><![CDATA[Biblical scholars claim to discover "Genesis death sandwich"]]></title>
 <h><![CDATA[Bible
∧Bible http://cbsnews.com/8301-205_162-57570703/biblical-scholars-claim-to-discover-genesis-death-sandwich/ ]]></h>
 <alt><![CDATA[2,8,32,128]]></alt>
 <bodys><![CDATA[Researchers using text-analysis software have found a new literary device in the first book of the Bible]]></bodys>
 <bodyn><![CDATA[10101010]]></bodyn>
 <meta><![CDATA[631]]></meta>
 <ref><![CDATA[94]]></ref>
 <url><![CDATA[http://api.snatz.com/index.php?app=asmapi&event=feeds&time=new&feed_id=14420571867616961140&item_id=12307444585169424103-13-02]]></url>
 <cdate>1376321299</cdate>
 <mmedia>0</mmedia>
 <bseo>0</bseo>
 <uid>2</uid>
 <sid>1</sid>
 <lang>255</lang>
 <afflags0>2</afflags0>
 <afflags1>24</afflags1>
 <afflags2>18</afflags2>
 <afflags3>2,8,32,128</afflags3>
 <afflags4>2,8,32,128</afflags4>
 <afflags5>2,8,32,128</afflags5>
 <afflags6>2,8,32,128</afflags6>
 <afflags7>2,8,32,128</afflags7>

 <afflags0ex>1,4,16,64</afflags0ex>
 <afflags1ex>1,4,16,64</afflags1ex>
 <afflags2ex>1,4,16,64</afflags2ex>
 <afflags3ex>1,4,16,64</afflags3ex>
 <afflags4ex>1,4,16,64</afflags4ex>
 <afflags5ex>1,4,16,64</afflags5ex>
 <afflags6ex>1,4,16,64</afflags6ex>
 <afflags7ex>1,4,16,64</afflags7ex>
</sphinx:document>
<sphinx:document id="9270465667525881884">
 <title><![CDATA[Election Result May Not Affect NASA Much]]></title>
 <h><![CDATA[<a href='http://6.mshcdn.com/wp-content/uploads/2012/11/obama-romney-composite.jpg' target=_blank><img src='http://6.mshcdn.com/wp-content/uploads/2012/11/obama-romney-composite.jpg' title='size: 0 width: 0 height: 0'></a>NASA
Republican
Mitt Romney
Barack Obama
∧NASA
∧Republican
∧Mitt∧Romney
∧Barack∧Obama http://mashable.com/2012/11/06/election-nasa/ Barack Obama
Mitt Romney
Washington
∧Barack∧Obama
∧Mitt∧Romney
∧Washington ]]></h>
 <alt><![CDATA[2,8,32,128]]></alt>
 <bodys><![CDATA[∧cities∧by∧GDP, ∧it∧people The outcome of today's presidential election is unlikely to have a profound impact on the future direction of American spaceflight and exploration, experts say.
While Republican candidate Mitt Romney has revealed few details about his space plans, a Romney Administration probably wouldn't dramatically alter the path NASA is currently pursuing under President Barack Obama, according to some observers.
"There are unlikely, as a result of the election, to be seismic changes," said space policy expert John Logsdon, a professor emeritus at George Washington University.
The Status Quo
In 2010, President Obama directed NASA to work toward getting astronauts to a near-Earth asteroid… Continue reading...
More About: 2012 presidential campaign, NASA, space]]></bodys>
 <bodyn><![CDATA[10101010]]></bodyn>
 <meta><![CDATA[1213]]></meta>
 <ref><![CDATA[94]]></ref>
 <url><![CDATA[http://api.snatz.com/index.php?app=asmapi&event=feeds&time=new&feed_id=16223976500889054516&item_id=9559378293515166420-12-11]]></url>
 <cdate>1376321299</cdate>
 <mmedia>0</mmedia>
 <bseo>0</bseo>
 <uid>2</uid>
 <sid>1</sid>
 <lang>255</lang>
 <afflags0>13</afflags0>
 <afflags1>30</afflags1>
 <afflags2>18</afflags2>
 <afflags3>2,8,32,128</afflags3>
 <afflags4>2,8,32,128</afflags4>
 <afflags5>2,8,32,128</afflags5>
 <afflags6>2,8,32,128</afflags6>
 <afflags7>2,8,32,128</afflags7>

 <afflags0ex>1,4,16,64</afflags0ex>
 <afflags1ex>1,4,16,64</afflags1ex>
 <afflags2ex>1,4,16,64</afflags2ex>
 <afflags3ex>1,4,16,64</afflags3ex>
 <afflags4ex>1,4,16,64</afflags4ex>
 <afflags5ex>1,4,16,64</afflags5ex>
 <afflags6ex>1,4,16,64</afflags6ex>
 <afflags7ex>1,4,16,64</afflags7ex>
</sphinx:document>
<sphinx:document id="9270471876072339482">
 <title><![CDATA[Zeebox adds Viacom to its repertoire of media partners, one week after US launch]]></title>
 <h><![CDATA[<a href='http://cdn.thenextweb.com/wp-content/blogs.dir/1/files/2012/10/tv-520x245.jpg' target=_blank><img src='http://cdn.thenextweb.com/wp-content/blogs.dir/1/files/2012/10/tv-520x245.jpg' title='size: 0 width: 0 height: 0'></a>Zeebox
Viacom
Comcast
announce
NBCUniversal
HBO & Cinemax
United States
∧Zeebox
∧Viacom
∧Comcast
∧announce
∧NBCUniversal
∧HBO∧∧∧Cinemax
∧United∧States http://thenextweb.com/media/2012/10/04/zeebox-adds-verizon-to-its-repertoire-of-media-partners-one-week-after-its-us-launch/ Australia
Comcast
News Corp.
Time Warner
United Kingdom
United States
announce
∧Australia
∧Comcast
∧News∧Corp∧
∧Time∧Warner
∧United∧Kingdom
∧United∧States
∧announce ]]></h>
 <alt><![CDATA[2,8,32,128]]></alt>
 <bodys><![CDATA[∧companies, ∧countries, ∧dic∧events It was a long-time coming, but last week we reported that UK-based second-screen app Zeebox finally launched in the US, where it has teamed up with a slew of broadcasters – 30 in total, including Comcast Cable, NBCUniversal, HBO &amp; Cinemax.
Now, however, it seems that media behemoth Viacom is also backing Zeebox for its US onslaught, joining the aforementioned companies “as strategic partners”, including investment, content and more. This is what Zeebox CEO and Co-Founder Ernesto Schmitt tweeted out earlier today:
Huge news: Viacom backs zeebox for the USA, joins NBCUniversal, Comcast and HBO as strategic partners with investment, content, promo.
&mdash; ernesto schmitt (@ErnestoSchmitt) October 4, 2012
This is a major development for Zeebox, and will go some way towards cementing itself at the forefront of the second screen space. Viacom is among the world’s largest media conglomerates, keeping company with the likes of Disney, Time Warner and News Corp. In real terms, this means that Zeebox will be able to tap content from the slew of of stations under Viacom’s remit – including Comedy Central, Logo, BET, Spike, TV Land, Nickelodeon, MTV, VH1, MTV2 and more.
Zeebox also launched in Australia earlier this summer, while in the UK it recently stepped up its existing efforts with Sky, after the broadcaster integrated a number of social features from Zeebox, bringing greater interaction to its audiences.
The service has seen impressive growth this year, and Schmitt revealed that it was seeing more than 15,000 new sign-ups every hour during the first weekend after its first TV advert aired in the UK.
Zeebox is going from strength to strength, and we’ll be sure to keep tabs on the company as it announces more partnerships.
Image Credit – Thinkstock]]></bodys>
 <bodyn><![CDATA[10101010]]></bodyn>
 <meta><![CDATA[2367]]></meta>
 <ref><![CDATA[93]]></ref>
 <url><![CDATA[http://api.snatz.com/index.php?app=asmapi&event=feeds&time=new&feed_id=16524082225408182211&item_id=9580661903103030451-12-10]]></url>
 <cdate>1376321299</cdate>
 <mmedia>0</mmedia>
 <bseo>0</bseo>
 <uid>2</uid>
 <sid>1</sid>
 <lang>255</lang>
 <afflags0>5</afflags0>
 <afflags1>30</afflags1>
 <afflags2>18</afflags2>
 <afflags3>2,8,32,128</afflags3>
 <afflags4>2,8,32,128</afflags4>
 <afflags5>2,8,32,128</afflags5>
 <afflags6>2,8,32,128</afflags6>
 <afflags7>2,8,32,128</afflags7>

 <afflags0ex>1,4,16,64</afflags0ex>
 <afflags1ex>1,4,16,64</afflags1ex>
 <afflags2ex>1,4,16,64</afflags2ex>
 <afflags3ex>1,4,16,64</afflags3ex>
 <afflags4ex>1,4,16,64</afflags4ex>
 <afflags5ex>1,4,16,64</afflags5ex>
 <afflags6ex>1,4,16,64</afflags6ex>
 <afflags7ex>1,4,16,64</afflags7ex>
</sphinx:document>
<sphinx:document id="9270494926982794359">
 <title><![CDATA[Games to keep an eye out for]]></title>
 <h><![CDATA[<a href='http://i.i.com.com/cnwk.1d/i/tim/2012/12/14/bioin_700x500.jpg' target=_blank><img src='http://i.i.com.com/cnwk.1d/i/tim/2012/12/14/bioin_700x500.jpg' title='size: 0 width: 0 height: 0'></a>United States
Game
eye
Price
∧United∧States
∧Game
∧eye
∧Price http://reviews.cnet.com/2300-13376_7-10016193.html?part=rss&subj=cnet&tag=title United States
∧United∧States ]]></h>
 <alt><![CDATA[2,8,32,128]]></alt>
 <bodys><![CDATA[∧countries 2013 is already at a record pace in terms of high-profile game releases. This spring keeps the momentum going with a number of blockbuster releases.Price: $60 Availability: March 26 The outlook: Easily the most anticipated title of the year, BioShock Infinite takes players to an alternate 1912 where a floating city in the sky called Columbia has seceded from the United States. Forced to recover a girl from the airborne metropolis, you'll learn of Columbia's mysterious secrets and shattered past. [Read more]]]></bodys>
 <bodyn><![CDATA[10101010]]></bodyn>
 <meta><![CDATA[989]]></meta>
 <ref><![CDATA[93]]></ref>
 <url><![CDATA[http://api.snatz.com/index.php?app=asmapi&event=feeds&time=new&feed_id=14983113245415276988&item_id=10987820760163512246-13-04]]></url>
 <cdate>1376321299</cdate>
 <mmedia>0</mmedia>
 <bseo>0</bseo>
 <uid>2</uid>
 <sid>1</sid>
 <lang>255</lang>
 <afflags0>2</afflags0>
 <afflags1>30</afflags1>
 <afflags2>18</afflags2>
 <afflags3>2,8,32,128</afflags3>
 <afflags4>2,8,32,128</afflags4>
 <afflags5>2,8,32,128</afflags5>
 <afflags6>2,8,32,128</afflags6>
 <afflags7>2,8,32,128</afflags7>

 <afflags0ex>1,4,16,64</afflags0ex>
 <afflags1ex>1,4,16,64</afflags1ex>
 <afflags2ex>1,4,16,64</afflags2ex>
 <afflags3ex>1,4,16,64</afflags3ex>
 <afflags4ex>1,4,16,64</afflags4ex>
 <afflags5ex>1,4,16,64</afflags5ex>
 <afflags6ex>1,4,16,64</afflags6ex>
 <afflags7ex>1,4,16,64</afflags7ex>
</sphinx:document>
<sphinx:document id="9270507129533609000">
 <title><![CDATA[New Starz Play website and apps stream only to Cox customers, but you might not need them]]></title>
 <h><![CDATA[<a href='http://www.blogcdn.com/www.engadget.com/media/2012/10/starzplay-iphone-ipad.jpg' target=_blank><img src='http://www.blogcdn.com/www.engadget.com/media/2012/10/starzplay-iphone-ipad.jpg' title='size: 0 width: 0 height: 0'></a>website
Netflix
Showtime
Starz Play
Cox customer
∧website
∧Netflix
∧Showtime
∧Starz∧Play
∧Cox∧customer http://engadget.com/2012/10/09/new-starz-play-website-and-apps-stream-only-to-cox-customers-bu/ 3G
Android
Comcast
Netflix
Wi-Fi
Xfinity
announce
iOS
iTunes
∧3G
∧Android
∧Comcast
∧Netflix
∧Wi∧Fi
∧Xfinity
∧announce
∧iOS
∧iTunes ]]></h>
 <alt><![CDATA[2,8,32,128]]></alt>
 <bodys><![CDATA[∧applications, ∧companies, ∧dic∧events, ∧mobile∧operating∧systems, ∧products, ∧service∧providers, ∧technologies, ∧wireless∧data∧standards Earlier this year Starz pulled its online content library back from Netflix and now it's relaunching the old Starz Play branded websites and apps (iOS and WiFi only for now, 3G and Android coming soon) for authenticated streaming, similar to HBO Go and Showtime Anytime. There's also an Encore Play site, and it plans to launch one for its Movieplex channel in the future. Currently, the services only support logins from Cox cable subscribers, but if you're not on that pay-TV provider you may not be missing out after all. Starz has already licensed its content to providers like Comcast for streaming through its Xfinity website and apps, deals which it tells The Hollywood Reporter cover about 70 percent of its customers. Like HBO and Showtime, this probably is not a prelude to offering its service beyond the tethers of cable and satellite, but as exec John Huguez puts it, "it is an expression of (Starz') brand and user interface." That likely only applies domestically however, as Starz also announced it's licensing its content to the cable-free HBO Nordic service, and one can see how building up its technology means it could serve up its own streams internationally some day. Even if you get Starz, if your provider is large enough to handle its own business when it comes to online services this probably won't affect you. However, for customers on smaller cable companies or in the future when deals get renegotiated, you may have another app to add to your drawer for TV Everywhere-style viewing.Continue reading New Starz Play website and apps stream only to Cox customers, but you might not need themFiled under: Home Entertainment, HDNew Starz Play website and apps stream only to Cox customers, but you might not need them originally appeared on Engadget on Tue, 09 Oct 2012 10:43:00 EDT. Please see our terms for use of feeds.Permalink&nbsp; &nbsp;|&nbsp; Starz Play, iTunes &nbsp;|&nbsp;Email this&nbsp;|&nbsp;Comments]]></bodys>
 <bodyn><![CDATA[10101010]]></bodyn>
 <meta><![CDATA[2493]]></meta>
 <ref><![CDATA[93]]></ref>
 <url><![CDATA[http://api.snatz.com/index.php?app=asmapi&event=feeds&time=new&feed_id=13401141354034017398&item_id=11742567228861401136-12-10]]></url>
 <cdate>1376321299</cdate>
 <mmedia>0</mmedia>
 <bseo>0</bseo>
 <uid>2</uid>
 <sid>1</sid>
 <lang>255</lang>
 <afflags0>3</afflags0>
 <afflags1>30</afflags1>
 <afflags2>18</afflags2>
 <afflags3>2,8,32,128</afflags3>
 <afflags4>2,8,32,128</afflags4>
 <afflags5>2,8,32,128</afflags5>
 <afflags6>2,8,32,128</afflags6>
 <afflags7>2,8,32,128</afflags7>

 <afflags0ex>1,4,16,64</afflags0ex>
 <afflags1ex>1,4,16,64</afflags1ex>
 <afflags2ex>1,4,16,64</afflags2ex>
 <afflags3ex>1,4,16,64</afflags3ex>
 <afflags4ex>1,4,16,64</afflags4ex>
 <afflags5ex>1,4,16,64</afflags5ex>
 <afflags6ex>1,4,16,64</afflags6ex>
 <afflags7ex>1,4,16,64</afflags7ex>
</sphinx:document>
<sphinx:document id="9270519987214782119">
 <title><![CDATA[Spoilers: Angry Olympics Fans Tweet Their Protests, NBC Responds]]></title>
 <h><![CDATA[<a href='http://www.bentonpena.org/wp-content/plugins/rss-poster/cache/15970_NBC_Olympics_Phelps-275x149.png' target=_blank><img src='http://www.bentonpena.org/wp-content/plugins/rss-poster/cache/15970_NBC_Olympics_Phelps-275x149.png' title='size: 0 width: 0 height: 0'></a>NBC
London
Olympics Fan
∧NBC
∧London
∧Olympics∧Fan http://bentonpena.org/marketing/spoilers-angry-olympics-fans-tweet-their-protests-nbc-responds.html London
NBC
Twitter
∧London
∧NBC
∧Twitter ]]></h>
 <alt><![CDATA[2,8,32,128]]></alt>
 <bodys><![CDATA[∧cities∧by∧GDP, ∧companies, ∧social∧network∧sites NBC, already in hot water with fans over its coverage of the London Olympics opening ceremonies, just can’t seem to catch a break. The broadcaster, which has chosen to tape-delay certain events, is catching heat from viewers upset after NBC broadcasters spoiled the outcome of the Michael Phelps – Ryan Lochte 400-meter individual medley showdown.
Instead of carrying the matchup live, NBC aired a taped interview with Phelps. After Lochte won the event by nearly 4 seconds with Phelps finishing a disappointing fourth, NBC Nightly News led with the surprising racing result before the event had aired on television. The hashtag #NBCsucks soon became a trending topic on Twitter, with fans taking to the social media site to voice their displeasure.
We’re with you, Michael Phelps: eight hour later! #NBCsucks
— pete_dude (@pete_dude) July 29, 2012
Jim Bell, the long-time Today Show executive producer who has taken over running Olympics coverage from star producer Dick Ebersol, has responded by answering fans’ questions on Twitter. Bell says NBC will make it explicit whether or not an event is live or tape-delayed and also warn viewers of spoilers.
@chemekimmi When live, there is almost always a “LIVE” graphic. When it’s tape, we always either say it and/or have graphic that says it.
— Jim Bell (@jfb) July 29, 2012
@MomInStL I have confirmed with my colleagues that a spoiler alert will be given. Thank you.
— Jim Bell (@jfb) July 29, 2012
Reaction from fans online so far has been mixed, with some viewers saying they will forgo Twitter altogether during the Games and others coming to terms with NBC’s tape-delayed coverage.
I’ve decided I’m okay with Olympic spoilers! I get just as happy/sad all over again when I get to watch the tape delay! #London2012
— Karen Pace (@KarenPace) July 29, 2012
What do you think of NBC’s Olympic coverage? Tell us how you’re following the latest news from the London Games in the comments.
Article source: http://feeds.mashable.com/~r/Mashable/~3/srYnnriBeMg/]]></bodys>
 <bodyn><![CDATA[10101010]]></bodyn>
 <meta><![CDATA[2580]]></meta>
 <ref><![CDATA[93]]></ref>
 <url><![CDATA[http://api.snatz.com/index.php?app=asmapi&event=feeds&time=new&feed_id=10716573351355983305&item_id=15092148758035725896-12-07]]></url>
 <cdate>1376321299</cdate>
 <mmedia>0</mmedia>
 <bseo>0</bseo>
 <uid>2</uid>
 <sid>1</sid>
 <lang>255</lang>
 <afflags0>2,8,32,128</afflags0>
 <afflags1>30</afflags1>
 <afflags2>1</afflags2>
 <afflags3>2,8,32,128</afflags3>
 <afflags4>2,8,32,128</afflags4>
 <afflags5>2,8,32,128</afflags5>
 <afflags6>2,8,32,128</afflags6>
 <afflags7>2,8,32,128</afflags7>

 <afflags0ex>1,4,16,64</afflags0ex>
 <afflags1ex>1,4,16,64</afflags1ex>
 <afflags2ex>1,4,16,64</afflags2ex>
 <afflags3ex>1,4,16,64</afflags3ex>
 <afflags4ex>1,4,16,64</afflags4ex>
 <afflags5ex>1,4,16,64</afflags5ex>
 <afflags6ex>1,4,16,64</afflags6ex>
 <afflags7ex>1,4,16,64</afflags7ex>
</sphinx:document>
<sphinx:document id="9270530354718812039">
 <title><![CDATA[Sharp AQUOS 206SH debuts 5″ CG-S 1080p display and two day battery]]></title>
 <h><![CDATA[<a href='http://cdn.slashgear.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/05/sharp_aquos_phone_xx_softbank_206sh_0.jpg' target=_blank><img src='http://cdn.slashgear.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/05/sharp_aquos_phone_xx_softbank_206sh_0.jpg' title='size: 0 width: 0 height: 0'></a>Sharp
Softbank
AQUOS Phone Xx
AQUOS 206SH
∧Sharp
∧Softbank
∧AQUOS∧Phone∧Xx
∧AQUOS∧206SH http://slashgear.com/sharp-aquos-206sh-debuts-5-cg-s-1080p-display-and-two-day-battery-07280832/ Android
Android 4
Galaxy Note
LTE
Samsung
Sharp
Softbank
Wi-Fi
gadget
∧Android
∧Android∧4
∧Galaxy∧Note
∧LTE
∧Samsung
∧Sharp
∧Softbank
∧Wi∧Fi
∧gadget ]]></h>
 <alt><![CDATA[2,8,32,128]]></alt>
 <bodys><![CDATA[∧companies, ∧mobile∧operating∧systems, ∧products, ∧wireless∧data∧standards Five-inch smartphones with 1080p displays aren’t uncommon now, but Sharp‘s new AQUOS Phone Xx SoftBank 206SH does have one advantage: enough battery life to get it through a promised two full days. The new handset, part of Japanese carrier SoftBank’s Summer 2013 line-up, uses a combination of old and new tech to help subscribers skip the overnight charge, with a huge battery paired with a clever CG Silicon TFT LCD display.
On the old-tech side, Sharp squeezes a massive 3,080 mAh battery into the 5-inch phone, only slightly smaller than the pack Samsung fits to the larger Galaxy Note II. With Sharp’s “Eco Tech” settings enabled – which seems to involve throttling the 1.7GHz Snapdragon S4 Pro quadcore processor (APQ8064) at times – the phone will supposedly last through two days of use.
However, the CG Silicon display also weighs in with some improvements of its own, using continuous grain silicon for the backplane rather than the amorphous silicon more traditionally found in LCD TFT panels. That, Sharp says, makes for a thinner and better-performing display, with higher quality graphics and reduced power consumption.
Interestingly, Sharp sees CG Silicon technology as a way to eventually build an entire computer on a single sheet of glass, in effect creating smartphones and mobile devices that were one, fused gadget rather than a selection of sandwiched individual parts. Exactly when that will be feasible remains to be seen, however; Sharp has created demo rigs with processors embedded into the substrate, but commercial applications haven’t been begun yet.
Instead, we get the 206SH and the 5-inch, 443ppi display Sharp showed off at CEATEC last year. Since then, the company has slapped on a touchscreen layer, of course, though the smaller number of overall layers should still pay dividends on display visibility.
Sharp has a track record of trialling new panel technology in devices for the Japanese market. Last year, the company released the AQUOS TAB SHT21, a 7-inch Android tablet using an IGZO display rather than LCD TFT or OLED. IGZO promises either roughly twice the runtime as an LCD panel at the same brightness, or as much as twice the brightness for outdoor usability, though manufacturing yields have meant the tech is yet to comprehensively spread.
The Sharp AQUOS Phone Xx SoftBank 206SH will go on sale in late June. It has a 13.1-megapixel camera with f/1.9 optics, 1-Seg digital TV, LTE, and runs Android 4.2, while wireless options include WiFi a/b/g/n/ac and Bluetooth 4.0 along with infrared. It’s also waterproof, and will be offered with a desktop dock for charging and entertainment use.
Sharp AQUOS 206SH debuts 5″ CG-S 1080p display and two day battery is written by Chris Davies & originally posted on SlashGear. © 2005 - 2012, SlashGear. All right reserved.]]></bodys>
 <bodyn><![CDATA[10101010]]></bodyn>
 <meta><![CDATA[3377]]></meta>
 <ref><![CDATA[94]]></ref>
 <url><![CDATA[http://api.snatz.com/index.php?app=asmapi&event=feeds&time=new&feed_id=10048318847061052429&item_id=11761097276766693129-13-05]]></url>
 <cdate>1376321299</cdate>
 <mmedia>0</mmedia>
 <bseo>0</bseo>
 <uid>2</uid>
 <sid>1</sid>
 <lang>255</lang>
 <afflags0>2</afflags0>
 <afflags1>30</afflags1>
 <afflags2>18</afflags2>
 <afflags3>2,8,32,128</afflags3>
 <afflags4>2,8,32,128</afflags4>
 <afflags5>2,8,32,128</afflags5>
 <afflags6>2,8,32,128</afflags6>
 <afflags7>2,8,32,128</afflags7>

 <afflags0ex>1,4,16,64</afflags0ex>
 <afflags1ex>1,4,16,64</afflags1ex>
 <afflags2ex>1,4,16,64</afflags2ex>
 <afflags3ex>1,4,16,64</afflags3ex>
 <afflags4ex>1,4,16,64</afflags4ex>
 <afflags5ex>1,4,16,64</afflags5ex>
 <afflags6ex>1,4,16,64</afflags6ex>
 <afflags7ex>1,4,16,64</afflags7ex>
</sphinx:document>
<sphinx:document id="9270536775909084641">
 <title><![CDATA[Google Expands Universal Search to Include Your Calendar]]></title>
 <h><![CDATA[<a href='http://www.webmonkey.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/02/gcalresults.png' target=_blank><img src='http://www.webmonkey.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/02/gcalresults.png' title='size: 0 width: 0 height: 0'></a>Image
Google
Search
∧Image
∧Google
∧Search http://webmonkey.com/2013/02/google-expands-universal-search-to-include-your-calendar/ Google
Google Drive
United States
∧Google
∧Google∧Drive
∧United∧States ]]></h>
 <alt><![CDATA[2,8,32,128]]></alt>
 <bodys><![CDATA[∧companies, ∧countries, ∧file∧hosting∧services, ∧search∧engines Your calendar, now part of your search results. Image: GoogleGoogle has expanded the personalized search “field trial” it initiated last year, pulling in additional results from Google Calendar. Your Google Calendar appointments join your Gmail and Google Drive documents alongside traditional Google search results for an all-in-one Google search experience.
If you’d like to participate, head on over to the signup page and add your account. Once that’s done, just log in to your Google account. You’ll then be able to search Gmail, your Google Drive documents and now your Google Calendar appointments directly from the Google search page (or from within Gmail). The Google Calendar integration doesn’t just add appointments, it also features support for natural language queries. For example, type “what is on my calendar today” and you’ll see the day’s agenda. More specific queries work as well; to find out when you’re meeting someone, just type “when am I meeting” and the person’s name.
Note that the personalized search trial is still only available to U.S. users with @gmail.com addresses (Google Apps accounts are out of luck for now). If you opt in and decide you hate it, you can always go back to the sign up page and turn universal search off.]]></bodys>
 <bodyn><![CDATA[10101010]]></bodyn>
 <meta><![CDATA[1770]]></meta>
 <ref><![CDATA[93]]></ref>
 <url><![CDATA[http://api.snatz.com/index.php?app=asmapi&event=feeds&time=new&feed_id=16831114575425217592&item_id=16801945444660315134-13-02]]></url>
 <cdate>1376321299</cdate>
 <mmedia>0</mmedia>
 <bseo>0</bseo>
 <uid>2</uid>
 <sid>1</sid>
 <lang>255</lang>
 <afflags0>2,8,32,128</afflags0>
 <afflags1>30</afflags1>
 <afflags2>1</afflags2>
 <afflags3>2,8,32,128</afflags3>
 <afflags4>2,8,32,128</afflags4>
 <afflags5>2,8,32,128</afflags5>
 <afflags6>2,8,32,128</afflags6>
 <afflags7>2,8,32,128</afflags7>

 <afflags0ex>1,4,16,64</afflags0ex>
 <afflags1ex>1,4,16,64</afflags1ex>
 <afflags2ex>1,4,16,64</afflags2ex>
 <afflags3ex>1,4,16,64</afflags3ex>
 <afflags4ex>1,4,16,64</afflags4ex>
 <afflags5ex>1,4,16,64</afflags5ex>
 <afflags6ex>1,4,16,64</afflags6ex>
 <afflags7ex>1,4,16,64</afflags7ex>
</sphinx:document>
<sphinx:document id="9270537453070835049">
 <title><![CDATA[General Mills to pay $8.5M over yogurt health claims]]></title>
 <h><![CDATA[<a href='http://assets.bizjournals.com/twincities/news/General_Mills_logo*100.jpg?v=1' target=_blank><img src='http://assets.bizjournals.com/twincities/news/General_Mills_logo*100.jpg?v=1' title='size: 0 width: 0 height: 0'></a>Mills
company
∧Mills
∧company http://bizjournals.com/twincities/morning_roundup/2013/02/general-mills-to-pay-85m-over-yoplus.html?ana=RSS&s=article_search law
∧law ]]></h>
 <alt><![CDATA[2,8,32,128]]></alt>
 <bodys><![CDATA[∧dic∧events General Mills Inc. has agreed to pay $8.5 million to settle a class-action lawsuit that claimed the company oversold the benefits of a probiotic yogurt.
Food Business News reports that the lawsuit, which targeted General Mills' Yo-Plus yogurt, had argued that the Golden Valley-based company didn't have a scientific basis for claiming digestive benefits for the product in ads.
The suit, by one of the law firms that pursued a similar action against Dannon's Activia, was filed in 2011.
As part of…]]></bodys>
 <bodyn><![CDATA[10101010]]></bodyn>
 <meta><![CDATA[1047]]></meta>
 <ref><![CDATA[94]]></ref>
 <url><![CDATA[http://api.snatz.com/index.php?app=asmapi&event=feeds&time=new&feed_id=15880438750162531922&item_id=10154729101256013287-13-02]]></url>
 <cdate>1376321299</cdate>
 <mmedia>0</mmedia>
 <bseo>0</bseo>
 <uid>2</uid>
 <sid>1</sid>
 <lang>255</lang>
 <afflags0>2,8,32,128</afflags0>
 <afflags1>30</afflags1>
 <afflags2>18</afflags2>
 <afflags3>2,8,32,128</afflags3>
 <afflags4>2,8,32,128</afflags4>
 <afflags5>2,8,32,128</afflags5>
 <afflags6>2,8,32,128</afflags6>
 <afflags7>2,8,32,128</afflags7>

 <afflags0ex>1,4,16,64</afflags0ex>
 <afflags1ex>1,4,16,64</afflags1ex>
 <afflags2ex>1,4,16,64</afflags2ex>
 <afflags3ex>1,4,16,64</afflags3ex>
 <afflags4ex>1,4,16,64</afflags4ex>
 <afflags5ex>1,4,16,64</afflags5ex>
 <afflags6ex>1,4,16,64</afflags6ex>
 <afflags7ex>1,4,16,64</afflags7ex>
</sphinx:document>
<sphinx:document id="9270547909980160013">
 <title><![CDATA[Sun paywall set at £2 with access to Premier League football highlights]]></title>
 <h><![CDATA[<a href='http://static.guim.co.uk/sys-images/Guardian/About/General/2013/5/13/1368459073233/The-Sun-008.jpg' target=_blank><img src='http://static.guim.co.uk/sys-images/Guardian/About/General/2013/5/13/1368459073233/The-Sun-008.jpg' title='size: 0 width: 0 height: 0'></a>Sun
charge
Premier League football highlight
∧Sun
∧charge
∧Premier∧League∧football∧highlight http://guardian.co.uk/media/2013/may/13/sun-paywall-premier-league-football BSkyB
Facebook
Sun
Twitter
United Kingdom
Yahoo
∧BSkyB
∧Facebook
∧Sun
∧Twitter
∧United∧Kingdom
∧Yahoo ]]></h>
 <alt><![CDATA[2,8,32,128]]></alt>
 <bodys><![CDATA[∧companies, ∧computer∧hardware∧manufacturers, ∧countries, ∧search∧engines, ∧social∧network∧sites Charge will come into effect in August after £30m deal is struck for rights to all 380 Premier League matches a seasonThe Sun is to introduce a paywall from 1 August with a £2 per week charge, including access to Premier League football highlights.Mike Darcey, the chief executive of News International who was responsible for striking the Premier League digital rights deal in January, said that the new service will be called Sun+."This move ensures that we will be offering a compelling, paid-for package across all of our titles, delivering great value for news that is worth paying for," he said, in an internal email to staff.Darcey said the package will include a "suite of offerings" including seven-day access to the Sun online, via tablet and smartphone apps. It will include access to Premier League clips as well as "exclusive offers and promotions".Darcey, the former chief operating officer at News Corporation-controlled BSkyB, was appointed chief executive of News International in December.He officially began at Wapping in January and moved swiftly to make his mark by striking a £30m-plus deal to snatch the exclusive rights to internet and mobile highlights for all 380 Premier League matches on the Sun, the Times and the Sunday Times digital platforms.In doing so he outbid his former employer, BSkyB, and easily outbid previous rights holders ESPN and Yahoo, which controlled parts of the digital rights that were previously split into different packages.For Darcey, a veteran of at least five Premier League TV rights auctions at BSkyB, the deal formed the basis of building a strategy to make the Sun a compelling enough digital product to erect a paywall.The UK's biggest selling daily newspaper has always been free online, but has only increased its digital readership by about 5 million monthly users to 27 million in four years.By comparison, over the same time period the Mail Online has gone from the fourth biggest UK newspaper with 23 million monthly users to the world's biggest with more than 110 million.In March, Darcey said it was "untenable" for the Sun to not charge for online content.The move means all of News International's national newspapers, including the Times and Sunday Times, are now behind paywalls.• To contact the MediaGuardian news desk email media@guardian.co.uk or phone 020 3353 3857. For all other inquiries please call the main Guardian switchboard on 020 3353 2000. If you are writing a comment for publication, please mark clearly "for publication".• To get the latest media news to your desktop or mobile, follow MediaGuardian on Twitter and Facebook.The SunPaywallsSports rightsDigital mediaNewspapers & magazinesNational newspapersNewspapersMedia businessNews InternationalInternetMark Sweneyguardian.co.uk &copy; 2013 Guardian News and Media Limited or its affiliated companies. All rights reserved. | Use of this content is subject to our Terms & Conditions | More Feeds&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;]]></bodys>
 <bodyn><![CDATA[10101010]]></bodyn>
 <meta><![CDATA[3484]]></meta>
 <ref><![CDATA[93]]></ref>
 <url><![CDATA[http://api.snatz.com/index.php?app=asmapi&event=feeds&time=new&feed_id=15734708125508751561&item_id=13404360252458163848-13-05]]></url>
 <cdate>1376321299</cdate>
 <mmedia>0</mmedia>
 <bseo>0</bseo>
 <uid>2</uid>
 <sid>1</sid>
 <lang>255</lang>
 <afflags0>1</afflags0>
 <afflags1>30</afflags1>
 <afflags2>18</afflags2>
 <afflags3>2,8,32,128</afflags3>
 <afflags4>2,8,32,128</afflags4>
 <afflags5>2,8,32,128</afflags5>
 <afflags6>2,8,32,128</afflags6>
 <afflags7>2,8,32,128</afflags7>

 <afflags0ex>1,4,16,64</afflags0ex>
 <afflags1ex>1,4,16,64</afflags1ex>
 <afflags2ex>1,4,16,64</afflags2ex>
 <afflags3ex>1,4,16,64</afflags3ex>
 <afflags4ex>1,4,16,64</afflags4ex>
 <afflags5ex>1,4,16,64</afflags5ex>
 <afflags6ex>1,4,16,64</afflags6ex>
 <afflags7ex>1,4,16,64</afflags7ex>
</sphinx:document>
<sphinx:document id="9270553842189294202">
 <title><![CDATA[When it comes to maps, Android co-founder thinks Apple lost its way]]></title>
 <h><![CDATA[Google
Android
Rich Miner
Apple Maps
∧Google
∧Android
∧Rich∧Miner
∧Apple∧Maps http://gigaom.com/mobile/when-it-comes-to-maps-android-co-founder-thinks-apple-lost-its-way/ Android
Apple
Apple Maps
Google
RIM
iOS
∧Android
∧Apple
∧Apple∧Maps
∧Google
∧RIM
∧iOS ]]></h>
 <alt><![CDATA[2,8,32,128]]></alt>
 <bodys><![CDATA[∧companies, ∧mobile∧operating∧systems, ∧products, ∧search∧engines, ∧web∧map∧services Rich Miner — who co-founded Android, sold it to Google and now is a partner at Google Ventures — tried using the new Apple Maps to get to a meeting this morning and got lost, making him late for the meeting. Miner told Om Malik at GigaOM Mobilize on Thursday afternoon regarding Apple’s decision to create Maps: “There’s build and there’s buy, and they decided to build and I’m not sure that was the right decision.”
Miner’s thoughts on Apple Maps was just one of the many topics of conversation during the interview. Carriers are another group that Miner thinks have made their fair share of mistakes over the years. Carriers own billing and they own the network and they haven’t really taken advantage of those to add value to the user interface or to create an app ecosystem, Miner said, adding “They just let that train leave the station.”
Carriers just keep conceding, says Miner. Back when Miner co-founded Android, he says one of the goals was to help carriers create a user interface and experience for their customers. But that was before Google bought the software startup, and it is now using it as the cornerstone of its mobile strategy.
When Miner looks back at where Android was then and where it is today, he said one of the few surprising things is that it was hard to predict the quick rate of of consumer adoption. Adoption of Android and Apple’s iOS has been so fast, that it’s clear that “people didn’t really understand how frustrated people were,” with the poor user mobile experiences before that.
Now Miner invests in startups for Google’ venture arm. He said he is excited about startups that can use mobile apps to change the enterprise, and gave a shout-out to PlanGrid, which has a blueprint app for the construction industry, and which Google Ventures backed. In particular, RIM has lost so much market cap over the years, Miner says he thinks that will deliver a lot of opportunity for new mobile enterprise innovation.
Check out the rest of our Mobilize 2012 coverage here, and the live stream can be found here.]]></bodys>
 <bodyn><![CDATA[10101010]]></bodyn>
 <meta><![CDATA[2605]]></meta>
 <ref><![CDATA[94]]></ref>
 <url><![CDATA[http://api.snatz.com/index.php?app=asmapi&event=feeds&time=new&feed_id=10063382566111140287&item_id=9964017271455783429-12-09]]></url>
 <cdate>1376321299</cdate>
 <mmedia>0</mmedia>
 <bseo>0</bseo>
 <uid>2</uid>
 <sid>1</sid>
 <lang>255</lang>
 <afflags0>31</afflags0>
 <afflags1>30</afflags1>
 <afflags2>18</afflags2>
 <afflags3>2,8,32,128</afflags3>
 <afflags4>2,8,32,128</afflags4>
 <afflags5>2,8,32,128</afflags5>
 <afflags6>2,8,32,128</afflags6>
 <afflags7>2,8,32,128</afflags7>

 <afflags0ex>1,4,16,64</afflags0ex>
 <afflags1ex>1,4,16,64</afflags1ex>
 <afflags2ex>1,4,16,64</afflags2ex>
 <afflags3ex>1,4,16,64</afflags3ex>
 <afflags4ex>1,4,16,64</afflags4ex>
 <afflags5ex>1,4,16,64</afflags5ex>
 <afflags6ex>1,4,16,64</afflags6ex>
 <afflags7ex>1,4,16,64</afflags7ex>
</sphinx:document>
<sphinx:document id="9270559627681457669">
 <title><![CDATA[ABC's 'The Bachelor' holding casting call at Maryland Live]]></title>
 <h><![CDATA[<a href='http://assets.bizjournals.com/baltimore/news/Bachelor-logo*100.jpg?v=1' target=_blank><img src='http://assets.bizjournals.com/baltimore/news/Bachelor-logo*100.jpg?v=1' title='size: 0 width: 0 height: 0'></a>Maryland
ABC
love
∧Maryland
∧ABC
∧love http://bizjournals.com/washington/news/2013/06/12/abcs-the-bachelor-holding-casting.html?ana=RSS&s=article_search Baltimore
Maryland
TV
june
love
∧Baltimore
∧Maryland
∧TV
∧june
∧love ]]></h>
 <alt><![CDATA[2,8,32,128]]></alt>
 <bodys><![CDATA[∧cities∧by∧GDP, ∧common∧trends Producers for ABC's "The Bachelor" are taking the true love found on reality television and bringing it to the most romantic place on earth — a casino. The Bachelor will hold an open casting call for bachelors and bachelorettes on June 13 from 5 p.m. to 9 p.m. at Rams Head Center Stage at Maryland Live Casino in Hanover. Producers are looking for men and women from the Baltimore area to appear on upcoming episodes of the hit TV show. The Bachelor also encourages candidates to also prepare.]]></bodys>
 <bodyn><![CDATA[10101010]]></bodyn>
 <meta><![CDATA[1044]]></meta>
 <ref><![CDATA[93]]></ref>
 <url><![CDATA[http://api.snatz.com/index.php?app=asmapi&event=feeds&time=new&feed_id=15880438750162531922&item_id=16331510056794431653-13-06]]></url>
 <cdate>1376321299</cdate>
 <mmedia>0</mmedia>
 <bseo>0</bseo>
 <uid>2</uid>
 <sid>1</sid>
 <lang>255</lang>
 <afflags0>6</afflags0>
 <afflags1>30</afflags1>
 <afflags2>18</afflags2>
 <afflags3>2,8,32,128</afflags3>
 <afflags4>2,8,32,128</afflags4>
 <afflags5>2,8,32,128</afflags5>
 <afflags6>2,8,32,128</afflags6>
 <afflags7>2,8,32,128</afflags7>

 <afflags0ex>1,4,16,64</afflags0ex>
 <afflags1ex>1,4,16,64</afflags1ex>
 <afflags2ex>1,4,16,64</afflags2ex>
 <afflags3ex>1,4,16,64</afflags3ex>
 <afflags4ex>1,4,16,64</afflags4ex>
 <afflags5ex>1,4,16,64</afflags5ex>
 <afflags6ex>1,4,16,64</afflags6ex>
 <afflags7ex>1,4,16,64</afflags7ex>
</sphinx:document>
<sphinx:document id="9270603738234914787">
 <title><![CDATA[Trilogy Technologies listed among world’s top managed service providers]]></title>
 <h><![CDATA[MSPmentor 501
∧MSPmentor∧501 http://siliconrepublic.com/strategy/item/31573-trilogy-technologies-listed ]]></h>
 <alt><![CDATA[2,8,32,128]]></alt>
 <bodys><![CDATA[Dublin-based Trilogy Technologies has been listed in the Nine Lives MSPmentor 501, a distinguished list and report identifying the world’s top managed service providers.Trilogy Technologies has been listed on the MSPmentor 50 EMEA edition and its managing director Edel Creely has been listed in the MSPmentor 250 list, which identifies the world’s top MSP experts and entrepreneurs.The MSPmentor 501 report is based on data from MSPmentor’s global online survey conducted from October to December 2012. The MSPmentor 501 report recognises top managed service providers based on a range of metrics, including annual managed services revenue growth, revenue per employee, managed services offered and customer devices managed.“We are honoured to be recognised by MSPmentor,” said Creely. “We believe our rankings highlight the market demand for a complete and affordable range of managed services for customers. “We identify the best aspects of managed services worldwide and bring that to our offering. We work to a best-of-breed worldwide agenda and this ranking reflects that,” Creely added.]]></bodys>
 <bodyn><![CDATA[10101010]]></bodyn>
 <meta><![CDATA[1621]]></meta>
 <ref><![CDATA[94]]></ref>
 <url><![CDATA[http://api.snatz.com/index.php?app=asmapi&event=feeds&time=new&feed_id=17523692694775832746&item_id=10514815318249127074-13-02]]></url>
 <cdate>1376321299</cdate>
 <mmedia>0</mmedia>
 <bseo>0</bseo>
 <uid>2</uid>
 <sid>1</sid>
 <lang>255</lang>
 <afflags0>2,8,32,128</afflags0>
 <afflags1>24</afflags1>
 <afflags2>18</afflags2>
 <afflags3>2,8,32,128</afflags3>
 <afflags4>2,8,32,128</afflags4>
 <afflags5>2,8,32,128</afflags5>
 <afflags6>2,8,32,128</afflags6>
 <afflags7>2,8,32,128</afflags7>

 <afflags0ex>1,4,16,64</afflags0ex>
 <afflags1ex>1,4,16,64</afflags1ex>
 <afflags2ex>1,4,16,64</afflags2ex>
 <afflags3ex>1,4,16,64</afflags3ex>
 <afflags4ex>1,4,16,64</afflags4ex>
 <afflags5ex>1,4,16,64</afflags5ex>
 <afflags6ex>1,4,16,64</afflags6ex>
 <afflags7ex>1,4,16,64</afflags7ex>
</sphinx:document>
<sphinx:document id="9270614234010362484">
 <title><![CDATA[Should You Buy From Huawei?]]></title>
 <h><![CDATA[ZTE
Huawei
Congress
United States
∧ZTE
∧Huawei
∧Congress
∧United∧States http://informationweek.com/mobility/security/should-you-buy-from-huawei/240009059?cid=RSSfeed_IWK_All Huawei
United States
∧Huawei
∧United∧States ]]></h>
 <alt><![CDATA[2,8,32,128]]></alt>
 <bodys><![CDATA[∧companies, ∧countries Congress says U.S. companies should not purchase products from Chinese firms Huawei and ZTE, citing national security concerns. I say Congress is dealing more in fear than facts.]]></bodys>
 <bodyn><![CDATA[10101010]]></bodyn>
 <meta><![CDATA[673]]></meta>
 <ref><![CDATA[93]]></ref>
 <url><![CDATA[http://api.snatz.com/index.php?app=asmapi&event=feeds&time=new&feed_id=18141261405818328329&item_id=9312196587737396675-12-10]]></url>
 <cdate>1376321299</cdate>
 <mmedia>0</mmedia>
 <bseo>0</bseo>
 <uid>2</uid>
 <sid>1</sid>
 <lang>255</lang>
 <afflags0>2,8,32,128</afflags0>
 <afflags1>30</afflags1>
 <afflags2>1</afflags2>
 <afflags3>2,8,32,128</afflags3>
 <afflags4>2,8,32,128</afflags4>
 <afflags5>2,8,32,128</afflags5>
 <afflags6>2,8,32,128</afflags6>
 <afflags7>2,8,32,128</afflags7>

 <afflags0ex>1,4,16,64</afflags0ex>
 <afflags1ex>1,4,16,64</afflags1ex>
 <afflags2ex>1,4,16,64</afflags2ex>
 <afflags3ex>1,4,16,64</afflags3ex>
 <afflags4ex>1,4,16,64</afflags4ex>
 <afflags5ex>1,4,16,64</afflags5ex>
 <afflags6ex>1,4,16,64</afflags6ex>
 <afflags7ex>1,4,16,64</afflags7ex>
</sphinx:document>
<sphinx:document id="9270619492002915935">
 <title><![CDATA[Manage and Organize Your Kindle Ebooks with Scida]]></title>
 <h><![CDATA[<a href='http://cdn.appstorm.net/mac.appstorm.net/authors/richmoss/Screen-Shot-2013-02-08-at-4.16.12-PM.jpg' target=_blank><img src='http://cdn.appstorm.net/mac.appstorm.net/authors/richmoss/Screen-Shot-2013-02-08-at-4.16.12-PM.jpg' title='size: 0 width: 0 height: 0'></a>Kindle
Scida
nightmare
∧Kindle
∧Scida
∧nightmare http://mac.appstorm.net/reviews/productivity-review/manage-and-organize-your-kindle-ebooks-with-scida/ Kindle
iOS device
iPhoto
iTunes
∧Kindle
∧iOS∧device
∧iPhoto
∧iTunes ]]></h>
 <alt><![CDATA[2,8,32,128]]></alt>
 <bodys><![CDATA[∧applications, ∧products It can be a bit of a nightmare trying to manage a Kindle with a large ebook collection. You can organize them into categories on the device, but that’s frustratingly slow. You could use the official Kindle app, but that’ll only cover you for Amazon-purchased ebooks.
Enter Scida, a new app for organizing your ebooks and putting them on your Kindle(s). It makes managing Kindle ebooks a breeze, but this initial release is a bit light on features. Let’s take a look.
Kindle Management
Scida’s easy to set up and get running. Just tell it where to find your ebooks and it’ll sort through for the three formats it supports — MOBI, AZW, PRC. When you plug a supported Kindle in for the first time, it prompts you to give it a name and import an books on the device to your library.
Scida automatically recognizes your Kindle when you connect it to your computer. Supported devices are the Kindle Keyboard, Kindle 4, Kindle Touch, Kindle Black, and Kindle Paperwhite.
From there you’re faced with a management interface that should be like second nature to navigate if you’ve ever used iPhoto, iTunes, or any of their ilk. A panel on the left lets you move between the main library, your collections, and — if it’s connected — your Kindle. The main area is split between a list of ebooks and information about the selected book.
You can also get great at-a-glance information about the contents of your Kindle, similar to the Summary tab on each iOS device in iTunes. This is probably my favorite part of the app, even if it is mostly aesthetic.
Check out your Kindle’s stats, storage, and supported document formats at a glance.
Creating new collections gets tedious quickly, since there’s no way to auto-populate a collection with titles by particular authors, and the app doesn’t grab any metadata beyond title and author. You can sort the list of all books by author or title, and filter it by a search term, at least, which should make the process of selecting ebooks and popping them into categories slightly less painful.
Only title and author can be modified, too. If you’re hoping to import cover art, you’re out of luck — unless you do a bit of hacking around outside the app.
Here you can see the full extent of Scida’s editing options.
To add your own cover art, you’ll need to navigate into the bowels of OS X’s Library folder. Your local repository of Scida books is stored at ~/Library/Containers/com.clapsol.scida/Data/Documents/Scida Library. Each book is in a folder according to its author’s name. In that folder, you need to place a .jiff file with the same name as the book. To create a .jiff, just take a JPEG file and change its extension under the Get Info Finder command.
Where’s the Functionality?
Scida does just three things well — copying books from your library to your Kindle, importing your Kindle books to your library, and looking nice. Everywhere else, it falls short. Besides title and author (and occasionally cover art), it neither displays nor allows you to edit metadata — which means no publisher, publish date, or tags.
Calibre, a free open-source alternative, handles all this and more automatically — provided you’re willing to put up with its awful interface. Without touching a thing, I had it showing tags, publisher, correct cover art, and publish date for the majority of my books — including even the ones that I made from web pages with the Push to Kindle browser plugin.
Scida enters a field dominated by the ugly workhorse Calibre, which is really a fantastic app once you get used to it.
Scida doesn’t need to replicate even half of Calibre’s features to be great for Kindle ebook management, but it would do well to appropriate the parts that are relevant to its vision as a sort of iPhoto for ebooks.
If you want to organize your books into collections, and have those collections synced across devices, you’re in for some headaches. There is no syncing at all. To reproduce your library’s collections on your Kindle, you have to create them again, then select the source collection, select all of the books, and finally drag them onto the relevant Kindle collection label.
If you’re really OCD about your organization and you have a large library, the whole process could take hours. Why can’t you drag the collection labels between library and devices, at least? Why does right-clicking on a book in the list not bring up a contextual menu for that book, rather than whatever was last selected? The longer I used Scida, the more I questioned its design. What seems on first impression to be intuitive turns out to be far from it.
You may find that some behaviors of Scida don’t fit your established mental models — like this issue with right-clicking not bring up a menu for the last-selected item rather than the one right beneath the cursor.
I hope future updates not only add the features you’d expect, but also fixes these odd interface issues.
A Promising Start
Scida just came out. For a version 1.0 release, it’s showing great potential. The app is snappy, beautiful, and — aside from those few aforementioned interface quirks — easy to use. But this beauty has yet to blossom into a great tool.
It lacks syncing, metadata (beyond the absolute basics), custom cover art, other Kindle-supported file types (PDF, plain text), and reading/previewing ebooks, among other things. And I’d hesitate to call it ready for most users.
What it does offer is a clean, simple design, coupled with the right ideas for a killer ebook management app. Keep your eye on Scida; it’s destined for greatness. It’s just recently been released, and the developers have told us that they have a number of new features planned in the future, including potentially adding the option to read eBooks directly in the app. That’d make it a nice eBook library for the Mac itself, too. For now, though, it’s a nice app for managing your Kindle, and little more.]]></bodys>
 <bodyn><![CDATA[10101010]]></bodyn>
 <meta><![CDATA[6481]]></meta>
 <ref><![CDATA[94]]></ref>
 <url><![CDATA[http://api.snatz.com/index.php?app=asmapi&event=feeds&time=new&feed_id=15292385916162704246&item_id=12203594050363642842-13-02]]></url>
 <cdate>1376321299</cdate>
 <mmedia>0</mmedia>
 <bseo>0</bseo>
 <uid>2</uid>
 <sid>1</sid>
 <lang>255</lang>
 <afflags0>2</afflags0>
 <afflags1>30</afflags1>
 <afflags2>18</afflags2>
 <afflags3>2,8,32,128</afflags3>
 <afflags4>2,8,32,128</afflags4>
 <afflags5>2,8,32,128</afflags5>
 <afflags6>2,8,32,128</afflags6>
 <afflags7>2,8,32,128</afflags7>

 <afflags0ex>1,4,16,64</afflags0ex>
 <afflags1ex>1,4,16,64</afflags1ex>
 <afflags2ex>1,4,16,64</afflags2ex>
 <afflags3ex>1,4,16,64</afflags3ex>
 <afflags4ex>1,4,16,64</afflags4ex>
 <afflags5ex>1,4,16,64</afflags5ex>
 <afflags6ex>1,4,16,64</afflags6ex>
 <afflags7ex>1,4,16,64</afflags7ex>
</sphinx:document>
<sphinx:document id="9270645484578034584">
 <title><![CDATA["Critical but stable" world nods at more risk]]></title>
 <h><![CDATA[London
∧London http://reuters.com/article/2012/10/03/us-investment-growth-volatility-idUSBRE89206F20121003?feedName=topNews&feedType=RSS London
∧London ]]></h>
 <alt><![CDATA[2,8,32,128]]></alt>
 <bodys><![CDATA[∧cities∧by∧GDP LONDON (Reuters) - Like a patient in a critical but stable condition, the world economy may be in for years of low, spluttering growth and yet a lack of volatility may be acting as a green light for investors.]]></bodys>
 <bodyn><![CDATA[10101010]]></bodyn>
 <meta><![CDATA[742]]></meta>
 <ref><![CDATA[94]]></ref>
 <url><![CDATA[http://api.snatz.com/index.php?app=asmapi&event=feeds&time=new&feed_id=13587314786271368979&item_id=18359633549975071872-12-10]]></url>
 <cdate>1376321299</cdate>
 <mmedia>0</mmedia>
 <bseo>0</bseo>
 <uid>2</uid>
 <sid>1</sid>
 <lang>255</lang>
 <afflags0>2,8,32,128</afflags0>
 <afflags1>30</afflags1>
 <afflags2>18</afflags2>
 <afflags3>2,8,32,128</afflags3>
 <afflags4>2,8,32,128</afflags4>
 <afflags5>2,8,32,128</afflags5>
 <afflags6>2,8,32,128</afflags6>
 <afflags7>2,8,32,128</afflags7>

 <afflags0ex>1,4,16,64</afflags0ex>
 <afflags1ex>1,4,16,64</afflags1ex>
 <afflags2ex>1,4,16,64</afflags2ex>
 <afflags3ex>1,4,16,64</afflags3ex>
 <afflags4ex>1,4,16,64</afflags4ex>
 <afflags5ex>1,4,16,64</afflags5ex>
 <afflags6ex>1,4,16,64</afflags6ex>
 <afflags7ex>1,4,16,64</afflags7ex>
</sphinx:document>
<sphinx:document id="9270666532311390473">
 <title><![CDATA[Rove-ality Reality Ruined Romney]]></title>
 <h><![CDATA[Mitt Romney
∧Mitt∧Romney http://technologyquestions.com/community/threads/rove-ality-reality-ruined-romney.516673/ Mitt Romney
∧Mitt∧Romney ]]></h>
 <alt><![CDATA[2,8,32,128]]></alt>
 <bodys><![CDATA[∧it∧people ]]></bodys>
 <bodyn><![CDATA[10101010]]></bodyn>
 <meta><![CDATA[488]]></meta>
 <ref><![CDATA[93]]></ref>
 <url><![CDATA[http://api.snatz.com/index.php?app=asmapi&event=feeds&time=new&feed_id=11323826168387279589&item_id=15143108859755809099-12-11]]></url>
 <cdate>1376321299</cdate>
 <mmedia>0</mmedia>
 <bseo>0</bseo>
 <uid>2</uid>
 <sid>1</sid>
 <lang>255</lang>
 <afflags0>2,8,32,128</afflags0>
 <afflags1>14</afflags1>
 <afflags2>1</afflags2>
 <afflags3>2,8,32,128</afflags3>
 <afflags4>2,8,32,128</afflags4>
 <afflags5>2,8,32,128</afflags5>
 <afflags6>2,8,32,128</afflags6>
 <afflags7>2,8,32,128</afflags7>

 <afflags0ex>1,4,16,64</afflags0ex>
 <afflags1ex>1,4,16,64</afflags1ex>
 <afflags2ex>1,4,16,64</afflags2ex>
 <afflags3ex>1,4,16,64</afflags3ex>
 <afflags4ex>1,4,16,64</afflags4ex>
 <afflags5ex>1,4,16,64</afflags5ex>
 <afflags6ex>1,4,16,64</afflags6ex>
 <afflags7ex>1,4,16,64</afflags7ex>
</sphinx:document>
<sphinx:document id="9270671763564907479">
 <title><![CDATA[Study: Voice Apps Don’t Make Texting While Driving Any Safer]]></title>
 <h><![CDATA[<a href='http://cdn.thetechjournal.com/wp-content/uploads/2012/05/textdrive.jpg' target=_blank><img src='http://cdn.thetechjournal.com/wp-content/uploads/2012/05/textdrive.jpg' title='size: 0 width: 0 height: 0'></a>time driver
road accident
Voice Apps
∧time∧driver
∧road∧accident
∧Voice∧Apps http://thetechjournal.com/auto/study-voice-apps-dont-make-texting-while-driving-any-safer.xhtml Amazon.com
Seattle
Texas
∧Amazon∧com
∧Seattle
∧Texas ]]></h>
 <alt><![CDATA[2,8,32,128]]></alt>
 <bodys><![CDATA[∧cities∧by∧GDP, ∧companies In order to avoid road accidents, for a long time drivers have been advised not to text anyone while driving. But almost no one seemed to follow that advice. As people were not able or not interested to restrain themselves from texting while driving, so to keep their eyes focused on road, hands-free texting using voice-operated technology was legalized. Recently, a study has found that drivers who use voice recognition application to compose their text messages are just as distracted as drivers who choose to manually text while driving.
The research was conducted by Texas A&amp;M Transportation Institute. According to the research result, “using voice-to-text applications to send and receive text messages while driving do not increase driver safety compared to manual texting.”
On the other side some previous years’ reports say the following:
Police issued 149 citations and 292 warnings for inattentive driving between December 1, 2010, and April 10, 2013 in Appleton.
In 2011, inattentive driving was listed as a contributing factor in 21,778 of the state’s 112,516 crashes, including 98 deaths.
The National Highway Safety Traffic Administration reported that 3,331 people were killed in crashes involving distracted drivers in 2011, and an estimated 387,000 were injured.
Maj. Sandra Huxtable, director of the Bureau of Safety said, “Their attention is focused everywhere, except where it should be, which is on the road.”
Texas researchers believe that the driving public assumes that using an app to text is better than using the device in his/her hand. Besides, many drivers admitted that they felt safer using the voice recognition apps while driving.
Source: Texas A&amp;M
Thanks To: Post Crescent, The Seattle Times
Buy Cheapest Related Product From Amazon.com]]></bodys>
 <bodyn><![CDATA[10101010]]></bodyn>
 <meta><![CDATA[2315]]></meta>
 <ref><![CDATA[94]]></ref>
 <url><![CDATA[http://api.snatz.com/index.php?app=asmapi&event=feeds&time=new&feed_id=9459570256309655035&item_id=14783752417346033306-13-04]]></url>
 <cdate>1376321299</cdate>
 <mmedia>0</mmedia>
 <bseo>0</bseo>
 <uid>2</uid>
 <sid>1</sid>
 <lang>255</lang>
 <afflags0>2,8,32,128</afflags0>
 <afflags1>30</afflags1>
 <afflags2>1</afflags2>
 <afflags3>2,8,32,128</afflags3>
 <afflags4>2,8,32,128</afflags4>
 <afflags5>2,8,32,128</afflags5>
 <afflags6>2,8,32,128</afflags6>
 <afflags7>2,8,32,128</afflags7>

 <afflags0ex>1,4,16,64</afflags0ex>
 <afflags1ex>1,4,16,64</afflags1ex>
 <afflags2ex>1,4,16,64</afflags2ex>
 <afflags3ex>1,4,16,64</afflags3ex>
 <afflags4ex>1,4,16,64</afflags4ex>
 <afflags5ex>1,4,16,64</afflags5ex>
 <afflags6ex>1,4,16,64</afflags6ex>
 <afflags7ex>1,4,16,64</afflags7ex>
</sphinx:document>
<sphinx:document id="9270685574413170515">
 <title><![CDATA[Change the World Without Losing Yourself]]></title>
 <h><![CDATA[<a href='http://static2.hbr.org/pallotta/flatmm/hed/20120928_2.jpg' target=_blank><img src='http://static2.hbr.org/pallotta/flatmm/hed/20120928_2.jpg' title='size: 0 width: 0 height: 0'></a>Woodrow Wilson
Eleanor Roosevelt
∧Woodrow∧Wilson
∧Eleanor∧Roosevelt http://blogs.hbr.org/pallotta/2012/09/change-the-world-without-losin.html General Electric
Indiana
Toyota
announce
∧General∧Electric
∧Indiana
∧Toyota
∧announce ]]></h>
 <alt><![CDATA[2,8,32,128]]></alt>
 <bodys><![CDATA[∧cities∧by∧GDP, ∧companies, ∧dic∧events A hundred years ago, people didn't talk about changing the world — not in the way we speak of it today. In 1912, there weren't movements for the eradication of poverty or disease, or even an understanding of their scale. Then came Woodrow Wilson's dream of the League of Nations, Eleanor Roosevelt, and the formation of the United Nations. From there, Gandhi, the civil rights movement, and speeches by President and Robert Kennedy that declared, "We need men who dream of things that never were," and that spoke of "a new world society." There was Martin Luther King's "I have a dream" speech, delivered at the age of 34, and Neil Armstrong walking on the surface of the moon at the age of 38. Their youth brought a feeling of youthfulness to humanity itself, and gave people the sense that nothing is impossible. This moment in the long arc of history launched a change-the-world movement that never existed before, including change-the-world vocations on a major scale — from the Peace Corps to an explosion in the growth of opportunities in the nonprofit sector, which employs more than 10 million people today. And in the last decade or so, the genre has become even more refined: social enterprise, social entrepreneurship, L3C low-profit corporations, B corporations, the charitable endurance event industry, and more. New infrastructures have arisen to support it, from the Stanford Social Innovation Review, TED and Good, to the Social Enterprise Program at Harvard. Most major universities now have nonprofit management programs that didn't exist ten years ago. And courses on philanthropy are now even taught at the undergraduate level at Tufts, Brown, Indiana University, and many other colleges.
With the growth of these structures and opportunities has come an emphasis on doing, often to the exclusion of being. The competition to be the one who changes the world can be as cut-throat, if not more, than the competition among fast-food chains, or cosmetics companies, or movie studios. Witness the recent war between the Susan G. Komen Foundation and Planned Parenthood. Or Komen's efforts to protect its brand by discouraging others from using the phrase "for the Cure," or AIDS activists' assaults on the AIDS Rides. Lost in this new era is the notion that one can still make a difference in business, even absent any corporate social responsibility program. How would the charities trying to change the world operate without the manufacturers that make the equipment for their medical clinics, or without General Electric providing them with light bulbs? How would a "social enterprise" like PlanetTran, the hybrid car service, operate without Toyota, who makes the Prius, which constitutes their fleet? And in the absence of industrial farmers and national grocery chains, we would find ourselves in need of a great deal more charity, and a lot further away from the goal of changing the world, to boot.
Paradoxically, this new era of limitlessness often serves to limit the imaginations of the young people it attracts. It can obscure their real and natural passions. If you want to change the world, you have to go into the change-the-world sector, the times say. And so a young girl, whose calling — and whose value to the world — may really be to dance, or to build an industry, is hypnotized into becoming the fundraising director for an NGO. Imagine if someone had held up Gandhi to a young Frank Lloyd Wright, as Gandhi is held up to our young people today, and the incredible architect decided to go run a nonprofit soup kitchen as a result. What a tragedy. And what a setback that would have been for architecture and design. Individual economic futures are at risk, as well. While we may envision a new world, the donating public and nonprofit sector are still stuck philosophically in Puritan times, demanding that nonprofit employees work for sacrificial wages, as a sign that their hearts are in the right place. And in another paradox, they ask the people who would dream a new dream for the world to abandon the economic dreams they have for themselves. These are complicated times for making a true difference. Perhaps much more than they were for Amelia Earhart, Rosa Parks, and Henry Ford. So, what difference does being (as opposed to doing) make? Presence? Listening? What difference does passion make? Peace of mind? A slow pace? Excellence? What difference does industry make, when it creates new products and jobs that make life better for others? All of these things exist independent of the change-the-world sector. And, the change-the-world industry itself cannot possibly change the world if forced to play by a set of Puritan economic rules than fundamentally work against it — low wages, no charity stock market, disdain for advertising and marketing, and the expectation of immediate results. I get e-mails all the time from people who are grappling with these issues — many from students wondering whether they should go into the for-profit sector or the nonprofit sector, or asking how they can reconcile their dreams of a better world with the economic dreams they have for themselves. Others are from corporate executives feeling a dearth of purpose, and asking for career advice. Still others are from nonprofit leaders frustrated by a system that works against the dreams that brought them into the sector in the first place. People are suffering from a crisis of meaning, and not in small part because the definitions of meaning have been re-engineered by a culture confused about it itself. The feedback I get has inspired me to delve more deeply into these issues as part of the work that my company does with a specific curriculum called Change Course, which explores the intersection of money and meaning. Somehow the dream of changing the world ended up changing the quality of our dreams. It's not natural. When this era of profound human potential combines with authentic human passions, unlimited by artificial categories and boxes, then the world can really change, into something including — but far more profound than — the world without human suffering we have begun to imagine.]]></bodys>
 <bodyn><![CDATA[10101010]]></bodyn>
 <meta><![CDATA[6689]]></meta>
 <ref><![CDATA[94]]></ref>
 <url><![CDATA[http://api.snatz.com/index.php?app=asmapi&event=feeds&time=new&feed_id=12823771777164524472&item_id=10034246525768589842-12-09]]></url>
 <cdate>1376321299</cdate>
 <mmedia>0</mmedia>
 <bseo>0</bseo>
 <uid>2</uid>
 <sid>1</sid>
 <lang>255</lang>
 <afflags0>2,8,32,128</afflags0>
 <afflags1>30</afflags1>
 <afflags2>1</afflags2>
 <afflags3>2,8,32,128</afflags3>
 <afflags4>2,8,32,128</afflags4>
 <afflags5>2,8,32,128</afflags5>
 <afflags6>2,8,32,128</afflags6>
 <afflags7>2,8,32,128</afflags7>

 <afflags0ex>1,4,16,64</afflags0ex>
 <afflags1ex>1,4,16,64</afflags1ex>
 <afflags2ex>1,4,16,64</afflags2ex>
 <afflags3ex>1,4,16,64</afflags3ex>
 <afflags4ex>1,4,16,64</afflags4ex>
 <afflags5ex>1,4,16,64</afflags5ex>
 <afflags6ex>1,4,16,64</afflags6ex>
 <afflags7ex>1,4,16,64</afflags7ex>
</sphinx:document>
<sphinx:document id="9270702829922449445">
 <title><![CDATA[Mac Setups: Desk of an Electrical Engineer & Amateur Photographer]]></title>
 <h><![CDATA[<a href='http://cdn.osxdaily.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/03/amateur-photographer-mac-setup.jpg' target=_blank><img src='http://cdn.osxdaily.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/03/amateur-photographer-mac-setup.jpg' title='size: 0 width: 0 height: 0'></a>Amateur Photographer
Mac Setups
Bob C.
Engineer
∧Amateur∧Photographer
∧Mac∧Setups
∧Bob∧C∧
∧Engineer http://osxdaily.com/2013/03/10/mac-setups-desk-of-an-electrical-engineer-amateur-photographer/ Apple
Canon
Facebook
Google Plus
MacBook Pro
∧Apple
∧Canon
∧Facebook
∧Google∧Plus
∧MacBook∧Pro ]]></h>
 <alt><![CDATA[2,8,32,128]]></alt>
 <bodys><![CDATA[∧companies, ∧macbook∧models, ∧social∧network∧sites This weeks great Mac setup comes to us from Bob C., an Electrical Design Engineer and amateur photographer who uses his Mac setup for image editing and management. There’s a fair amount of audio equipment mixed in as well:
MacBook Pro 15″ Retina – Core i7 CPU, 8GB RAM, 256GB SSD
Apple Cinema Display 24″ connected to the MacBook Pro
iPad
iPhone 5
Full-sized Apple Keyboard
Apple Magic Trackpad
Apple Magic Mouse
Griffin Powermate USB media controller
M-Audio BX5a 70 watt Bi-amplified Studio Reference Monitors
Mackie 402-VLZ3 4-channel Mixer
Audio-Technica Pro49QL condenser microphone with AT8615 Desk Stand
Behringer UCA202 USB Audio Interface (not shown)
LaCie 256GB Rugged USB 3.0 and Thunderbold, for photo storage (with bright orange rubber bumper removed)
Segate 1GB USB 3.0 Backup Plus (for Time Machine backup)
Satechi 4 port USB3 Hub (not shown)
Though the MacBook Pro is shown in clamshell mode, Bob will often have the display open to function as a second monitor, an especially nice prospect given the gorgeous Retina display. For those wondering, it looks like the camera used to take this great desk shot and accurately capture the lighting is a Canon EOS Digital Rebel XSi (found via EXIF data!), presumably that’s the camera that gets most use for photography as well.
Do you have a Mac or Apple setup you want featured in our weekly setup highlight? Send submissions to us via email at osxdailycom@gmail.com, or you can post it on our Facebook page, send it to us there, or over on Google Plus. Please include a good picture or two, a list of hardware, and a brief description of what you use the gear for.]]></bodys>
 <bodyn><![CDATA[10101010]]></bodyn>
 <meta><![CDATA[2175]]></meta>
 <ref><![CDATA[94]]></ref>
 <url><![CDATA[http://api.snatz.com/index.php?app=asmapi&event=feeds&time=new&feed_id=12901156756416342578&item_id=14232842424967757991-13-03]]></url>
 <cdate>1376321299</cdate>
 <mmedia>0</mmedia>
 <bseo>0</bseo>
 <uid>2</uid>
 <sid>1</sid>
 <lang>255</lang>
 <afflags0>2,8,32,128</afflags0>
 <afflags1>30</afflags1>
 <afflags2>1</afflags2>
 <afflags3>2,8,32,128</afflags3>
 <afflags4>2,8,32,128</afflags4>
 <afflags5>2,8,32,128</afflags5>
 <afflags6>2,8,32,128</afflags6>
 <afflags7>2,8,32,128</afflags7>

 <afflags0ex>1,4,16,64</afflags0ex>
 <afflags1ex>1,4,16,64</afflags1ex>
 <afflags2ex>1,4,16,64</afflags2ex>
 <afflags3ex>1,4,16,64</afflags3ex>
 <afflags4ex>1,4,16,64</afflags4ex>
 <afflags5ex>1,4,16,64</afflags5ex>
 <afflags6ex>1,4,16,64</afflags6ex>
 <afflags7ex>1,4,16,64</afflags7ex>
</sphinx:document>
<sphinx:document id="9270727095482691537">
 <title><![CDATA[First Wood War brings a Unique RTS Game to Android]]></title>
 <h><![CDATA[<a href='http://android-apps.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/04/first.wood_.war-android.jpg' target=_blank><img src='http://android-apps.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/04/first.wood_.war-android.jpg' title='size: 0 width: 0 height: 0'></a>Wood War
Android
RTS game
∧Wood∧War
∧Android
∧RTS∧game http://android-apps.com/articles/first-wood-war-brings-a-unique-rts-game-to-android/ Android
∧Android ]]></h>
 <alt><![CDATA[2,8,32,128]]></alt>
 <bodys><![CDATA[∧mobile∧operating∧systems, ∧products If you’re looking for a great RTS game, there’s a new one called First Wood War that you’ll want to check out. It’s an epic game involving little wooden soldiers, but not the type of wooden soldiers you’re probably thinking of…]]></bodys>
 <bodyn><![CDATA[10101010]]></bodyn>
 <meta><![CDATA[740]]></meta>
 <ref><![CDATA[93]]></ref>
 <url><![CDATA[http://api.snatz.com/index.php?app=asmapi&event=feeds&time=new&feed_id=17039186454652086231&item_id=15431767642127402908-13-04]]></url>
 <cdate>1376321299</cdate>
 <mmedia>0</mmedia>
 <bseo>0</bseo>
 <uid>2</uid>
 <sid>1</sid>
 <lang>255</lang>
 <afflags0>2</afflags0>
 <afflags1>30</afflags1>
 <afflags2>18</afflags2>
 <afflags3>2,8,32,128</afflags3>
 <afflags4>2,8,32,128</afflags4>
 <afflags5>2,8,32,128</afflags5>
 <afflags6>2,8,32,128</afflags6>
 <afflags7>2,8,32,128</afflags7>

 <afflags0ex>1,4,16,64</afflags0ex>
 <afflags1ex>1,4,16,64</afflags1ex>
 <afflags2ex>1,4,16,64</afflags2ex>
 <afflags3ex>1,4,16,64</afflags3ex>
 <afflags4ex>1,4,16,64</afflags4ex>
 <afflags5ex>1,4,16,64</afflags5ex>
 <afflags6ex>1,4,16,64</afflags6ex>
 <afflags7ex>1,4,16,64</afflags7ex>
</sphinx:document>


</sphinx:docset>
